<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site. -->
<!-- It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content. -->
<!-- You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another. -->
<!-- This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site. -->

<!-- To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps: -->
<!-- 1. Log in to that site as an administrator. -->
<!-- 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel. -->
<!-- 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list. -->
<!-- 4. Activate & Run Importer. -->
<!-- 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page. -->
<!-- 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users -->
<!--    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an -->
<!--    existing user on the site or to create a new user. -->
<!-- 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc. -->
<!--    contained in this file into your site. -->

<!-- generator="WordPress/4.3.3" created="2016-03-12 22:54" -->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/"
>

<channel>
	<title>TRUE WORDPRESS</title>
	<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 22:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
	<wp:base_site_url>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress</wp:base_site_url>
	<wp:base_blog_url>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress</wp:base_blog_url>

	<wp:author><wp:author_id>1</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>admin</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>admin@truewordpress.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[admin]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>


	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=4.3.3</generator>

	<item>
		<title>Brand-by-brand guide to car infotainment</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/hello-world/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 06:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=1</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Automakers continue to innovate and push in-car entertainment boundaries. Most new vehicles’ systems can navigate to a destination, operate a smartphone hands-free, and an entire digital music collection over Bluetooth.

Problem is, some automakers’ systems are more cooperative and intuitive than others. The worst ones are distracting while driving, even after you figure them out. With less-intuitive systems, performing everyday tasks can be a problem. For instance, a conventional volume knob can be more user-friendly than a “haptic” touch-sensitive control. Everyday functions should be readily accessible, not buried in menus.
<div class="nativeAd show">
<div data-m="{&quot;n&quot;:&quot;InlineAppPromoByBing&quot;,&quot;y&quot;:17,&quot;l&quot;:&quot;9wzdncrdfxzs&quot;,&quot;i&quot;:125,&quot;o&quot;:3,&quot;p&quot;:&quot;52&quot;}" data-id="125"></div>
Wunderlist helps millions of people around the world capture their ideas, things to do and places to see. Whether you’...

</div>
Reliability can be another problem. Our latest Annual Auto Survey shows that buggy systems come from Cadillac, Chrysler, and Infiniti. Our charts highlight Consumer Reports’ findings of what each major automaker offers in its cars. Few infotainment systems are a slam dunk for usability and reliability, but most are evolving and improving.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>1</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 06:07:34</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 06:07:34</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>hello-world</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="auto"><![CDATA[auto]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="autos"><![CDATA[Autos]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[229]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkein.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:comment>
			<wp:comment_id>1</wp:comment_id>
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Mr WordPress]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url>https://wordpress.org/</wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_author_IP></wp:comment_author_IP>
			<wp:comment_date>2016-03-01 06:07:34</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>2016-03-01 06:07:34</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Hi, this is a comment.
To delete a comment, just log in and view the post&#039;s comments. There you will have the option to edit or delete them.]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
			<wp:comment_user_id>0</wp:comment_user_id>
		</wp:comment>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The 8 Best Reasons to Buy a New Car</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/the-8-best-reasons-to-buy-a-new-car/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=116</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[New cars are a poor investment. Instant, and sometimes dramatic, depreciation of a new car makes a lightly used car the smarter financial decision.

Aside from allowing someone else to absorb thousands of dollars in lost value, though, buying a used car is a bigger gamble. Furthermore, in an era when car companies make annual advances in terms of engineering and technology, vehicles age prematurely. A used car that is just a few years old may lack specific equipment that you want on your next vehicle.

Whether you should buy a new car or a used car is dependent on your specific situation. If you’re leaning toward a factory-fresh set of wheels, these are the 8 best reasons to buy a new car.

<span class="storyimage smallfullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" data-attrib="Provided by Daily News, L.P." data-caption="According to J.D. Power reliability is the most important factor when choosing a vehicle. - Christian Wardlaw" data-id="58" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:58,&quot;p&quot;:52,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:6}"><img class=" loaded" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpDlar.img?h=476&amp;w=635&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="According to J.D. Power reliability is the most important factor when choosing a vehicle. - Christian Wardlaw" width="635" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;64&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;48&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpDlar.img?h=476&amp;w=635&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size3column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;47&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpDlar.img?h=468&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size2column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;47&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpDlar.img?h=468&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" /></span></span>

<strong>1.) Reliability</strong>

According to J.D. Power, more than half of car buyers claim that after exterior and interior styling, reliability is the most important factor when choosing a vehicle. Because new cars are typically more reliable than used cars, consumers are likely better served by choosing a new one instead of a used one.

Qualified language is necessary here because reliability means different things to different people. Especially in recent years, consumer dissatisfaction with user experience and design has colored perceptions of quality and reliability.

For example, new car buyers frequently find touchscreen infotainment systems difficult and confusing to use. Dual-clutch automated manual transmissions that don’t sound or feel like traditional automatic transmissions produce a greater number of owner complaints. Misunderstood safety technology causes consternation in drivers.

Keep in mind that the modern definition of reliability encompasses matters of design, user experience, and expectations of operation in addition to outright component failure. Choosing a simpler, less complex vehicle is often the best path to trouble-free car ownership.

<img src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpDlao.img?h=476&amp;w=635&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="Whether you should buy a new car or a used car is dependent on your specific situation. - Christian Wardlaw" />

<strong>2.) Warranty</strong>

New cars come with a warranty, and some are quite generous. This means that if something does break or fails to work as designed or intended, you can get it replaced at no cost.

When it comes to warranty coverage, Hyundai and Kia provide the best programs, with Mitsubishi close behind. Buy a new Hyundai or Kia, and these automakers provide the following coverage:

• Powertrain warranty: 10 years or 100,000 miles

• Vehicle warranty: 5 years or 60,000 miles

• Rust warranty: 7 years with unlimited mileage

• Hybrid battery warranty: Guaranteed for the life of the vehicle

• Roadside assistance program: 5 years with unlimited mileage

In 2016, Toyota supplies the least favorable warranty program, supplying industry minimum coverage combined with the shortest roadside assistance program of any volume

<img src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpDlas.img?h=476&amp;w=635&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="After giving car companies advance notice that it was doing so, the IIHS developed the small overlap frontal impact crash test. - Volvo" />

<strong>3.) Safety</strong>

During the past half-decade, the Insurance Institute for Highway Safety (IIHS) has set the safety agenda and requirements for the automotive industry, pushing beyond the minimum standards required by the federal government.

After giving car companies advance notice that it was doing so, the IIHS developed the small overlap frontal impact crash test, which measures how well a vehicle’s underlying structure deflects collision force when an impact occurs at the front corner of a vehicle. This test is designed to replicate what happens when two vehicles collide on a 2-lane road where one driver has veered across the yellow line, or when a driver departs from the lane of travel and strikes a tree or other large object such as a parked car.

In turn, this new test and the passing grade that would lead to a “Top Safety Pick” designation led automakers to develop stronger and more robust vehicle structures that do a better job of protecting occupants.

Budgets being what they are, some companies have been caught cutting corners. For example, when Ford redesigned the F-150 pickup for the 2015 model year, Automotive News reported that the company installed steel structural enhancements to ensure top crash-test performance for the volume-selling crew cab version of the truck, but did not add them to the regular cab and extended cab models. Ford has since announced that it has applied such countermeasures to the 2016 model-year F-150.

A champion of collision avoidance technologies, the IIHS has also demonstrated how automatic emergency braking systems dramatically reduce the number of car accidents. Reserved for luxury-brand vehicles just a few years ago, many new mainstream vehicles offer this technology now, perhaps most notably the 2016 Scion iA, which costs $17,595.

<img src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpD5w7.img?h=476&amp;w=635&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="While CarFax reports and stronger laws have helped to reduce the possibility that a used car buyer might get stuck with someone else’s problem, a new car is rarely a problem. - Hyundai" />

<strong>4.) Fuel Economy</strong>

In 2025, the U.S. new vehicle fleet must average 54.5 mpg, posing quite a challenge for a market in which pickup trucks and SUVs are the most popular vehicle choices.

Nevertheless, automakers are rising to the challenge. From installing automatic engine stop/start systems and cylinder deactivation technologies to building new vehicles with lightweight materials and aerodynamic designs, new cars are more fuel-efficient than ever.

Though consumer interest in efficient vehicles is directly correlated to the price of gasoline, car companies must strive to meet federal regulations lest they face significant penalties. That means that a new car will almost always be more fuel-efficient than a used car. In turn, that means a new car will make its owner happier when gasoline prices spike again.

<img src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpDyic.img?h=486&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="" />

<strong>5.) Technology</strong>

Buttons and knobs are terrific, but a new generation of smartphone-native car shoppers is arriving in dealership showrooms. Internet connectivity, smartphone projection technology, voice-texting, and access to social media feeds are increasingly important to younger buyers. The newer the car, the more technologically advanced it will be.

This applies to safety technology, too. Collision avoidance technologies are proving to reduce accidents, and they are becoming more widely available in mainstream models. Honda is doing a particularly good job of making features such as forward collision warning, automatic emergency braking, and road departure prevention systems available at affordable price points. Now, if it would just swap LameWatch (excuse us, LaneWatch) for a proper blind spot warning system, it would be clearly leading the industry in this regard.

<img src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpDNLn.img?h=486&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="" />

<strong>6.) Big Discounts</strong>

Choose a new vehicle in a competitive segment, perhaps one that isn’t selling as well as its competition, perhaps one that is left over from the previous model year, and you can secure a big discount, one large enough to help offset the vehicle’s loss of value the moment you drive it away from the dealership.

If you have the luxury of choosing a specific time to buy, it is better to wait until the end of the month, the end of the model year, or the end of the calendar year. Some people may argue that this isn’t true. Until automakers stop providing dealerships with volume-based incentive programs, and stop competing for best-selling model or brand status, and better manage inventory levels in advance of new model year production, chances are good that your dealership will be more likely to wheel and deal at those times.

Also, keep in mind that if you’re buying a hot new model, or a vehicle in high demand and short supply, you’re not going to get a big discount. In fact, you may pay a price premium.

<img src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpDUpB.img?h=486&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="" />

<strong>7.) Attractive Financing</strong>

Historically low interest rates and vehicle loan terms that commonly span six years have made new car ownership a reality for more people. Financial institutions also typically offer more attractive interest rates for new vehicles than they do for used vehicles.

Yes, the payments for a new vehicle are higher than the payments for a used vehicle, and it takes longer to pay off a new vehicle loan. However, for as long as buyers can obtain no-interest and exceptionally low-interest car loans, a new car could be within the grasp of someone who might otherwise have no choice but to buy a used car.

<img src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpDQmE.img?h=486&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&amp;x=1254&amp;y=1159" alt="" />

<strong>8.) Knowing the Vehicle’s History</strong>

When you buy a new car, you know that vehicle’s history. You know how it was cared for, where it was serviced, how it was driven, and whether it was involved in an accident. When you buy a used car, you never really know for sure.

While CarFax reports and stronger laws have helped to reduce the possibility that a used car buyer might get stuck with someone else’s problem, a new car is rarely a problem. And when it is, a warranty protects the buyer.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>116</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:17:34</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:17:34</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>the-8-best-reasons-to-buy-a-new-car</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="autos"><![CDATA[Autos]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="travel"><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[245]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Reggie Bush’s 2013 Ford F-250 King Ranch</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/reggie-bushs-2013-ford-f-250-king-ranch/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=118</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[In college football, there is only one award given out that determines who the very best and most elite player is during that football season. It is considered the most prestigious of all awards at that level. In 2005, that award, the Heisman Trophy, was given to a then-20-year-old running back named Reggie Bush from the University of Southern California. As the second overall pick in the 2006 NFL Draft, Reggie had a lot to live up to. He landed with the New Orleans Saints and was part of the amazing 2010 run that won them a Super Bowl.

&nbsp;

There are many perks of being a superstar NFL running back, including advertisement benefits. As a member of the Miami Dolphins in 2012, Reggie did a promotional ad for Wayne Akers Ford in Lake Worth, Florida. In return for the advertisement, the company presented Reggie with a pristine, brand-new ’13 Ford F-250 King Ranch. Since Reggie’s flair for individuality wouldn’t allow him to leave the truck stock from the factory, he utilized DV8 Motorsports, a reputable company the dealership used regularly.

<span class="storyimage fullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" data-attrib="Provided by TruckTrend" data-caption="2013 Ford F250 King Ranch Reggie Bush 040" data-id="112" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:112,&quot;p&quot;:54,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:5}"><img class=" loaded" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1utJ.img?h=486&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&amp;x=908&amp;y=551" alt="2013 Ford F250 King Ranch Reggie Bush 040" width="728" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;73&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;49&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1utJ.img?h=486&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&amp;x=908&amp;y=551&quot;},&quot;size3column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1utJ.img?h=417&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&amp;x=908&amp;y=551&quot;},&quot;size2column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1utJ.img?h=417&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&amp;x=908&amp;y=551&quot;}}" /></span></span>

<span class="storyimage fullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="caption truncate"><span class="attribution">© Provided by TruckTrend</span> 2013 Ford F250 King Ranch Reggie Bush 040</span></span>

Almost immediately, the hardworking staff at DV8 Motorsports got down and dirty on the Super Duty for Reggie Bush. Chris Brooks took the reins and wrapped every inch of the Ford in a menacing flat black wrap. Shop owner Cary Jones got to work on the exterior additions, installing a Smittybilt M-1 mesh grille, HID conversion kits, a Rigid Industries bumper lightbar, and front and rear smoked lights. An Undercover Flex tonneau cover was added, along with a BedRug bedliner for transporting cleats and other football gear.
<div class="nativeAd show">
<div>
<div class="truncate">

Recommended for you: New Ford F-Series F-250 | truecar.com
<div>truecar.com/ford-f-series-f-250 | Sponsored</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<span class="storyimage fullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" data-attrib="Provided by TruckTrend" data-caption="2013 Ford F250 King Ranch Reggie Bush 002" data-id="113" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:113,&quot;p&quot;:54,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:6}"><img class=" loaded" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1pjK.img?h=486&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="2013 Ford F250 King Ranch Reggie Bush 002" width="728" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;73&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;49&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1pjK.img?h=486&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size3column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1pjK.img?h=417&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size2column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1pjK.img?h=417&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" /></span></span>

<span class="storyimage fullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="caption truncate"><span class="attribution">© Provided by TruckTrend</span> 2013 Ford F250 King Ranch Reggie Bush 002</span></span>

Once the body accessories were complete, the truck moved to Dan Winters at DV8 Motorsports for the suspension alteration. A full 11-inch lift was added using Fabtech spindles and 4.0 Dirt Logic coilovers in the front. The rear uses Fabtech leaf springs to support the heavy Ford. Moving to the wheel and tire section of DV8 Motorsports, a set of 24x14 American Force Alpha SF8 wheels wrapped in 38x13.50R24 Nitto Trail Grappler rubber set the foundation for the F-250.

<span class="storyimage fullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" data-attrib="Provided by TruckTrend" data-caption="2013 Ford F250 King Ranch Reggie Bush 056" data-id="114" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:114,&quot;p&quot;:54,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:7}"><img class=" loaded" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1pjS.img?h=486&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="2013 Ford F250 King Ranch Reggie Bush 056" width="728" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;73&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;49&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1pjS.img?h=486&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size3column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1pjS.img?h=417&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size2column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1pjS.img?h=417&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" /></span></span>

<span class="storyimage fullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="caption truncate"><span class="attribution">© Provided by TruckTrend</span> 2013 Ford F250 King Ranch Reggie Bush 056</span></span>

For the interior to match the exterior, Jarrett Penaluna painted the all-wooden trim in satin black. A Roadwire leather kit with a black perforated center insert was installed to flow with the all-black theme. LED lighting was added to the interior for a better visual showing. Jarrett began working on the tunes using the stock head unit. A 10-inch Memphis Audio subwoofer was placed in a custom ported box and powered by a Memphis Audio MRA amplifier. Memphis 5x7 midrange speakers were lined throughout the cabin for crystal clear audio sound.

<span class="storyimage fullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" data-attrib="Provided by TruckTrend" data-caption="2013 Ford F250 King Ranch Reggie Bush 051" data-id="115" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:115,&quot;p&quot;:54,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:8}"><img class=" loaded" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1pjU.img?h=486&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="2013 Ford F250 King Ranch Reggie Bush 051" width="728" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;73&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;49&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1pjU.img?h=486&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size3column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1pjU.img?h=417&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size2column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq1pjU.img?h=417&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" /></span></span>

<span class="storyimage fullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="caption truncate"><span class="attribution">© Provided by TruckTrend</span> 2013 Ford F250 King Ranch Reggie Bush 051</span></span>

Although injuries marred Reggie’s 2015 season with the San Francisco 49ers, the birth of his son Uriah and raising of his daughter Briseis with wife Lilit Avagyan gave him much to look forward to. With new beginnings and an introduction to fatherhood, Reggie’s DV8 Motorsports–built Ford F-250 will be in his family for a long time to come. “I look forward to hitting the streets in this beast,” Reggie tells us. “I can only imagine the new]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>118</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:20:18</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:20:18</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>reggie-bushs-2013-ford-f-250-king-ranch</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="auto"><![CDATA[auto]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="autos"><![CDATA[Autos]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="travel"><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[243]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Interview: Chevrolet’s Camaro Chief on Track Simulation Models, Mustang Rivalry</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/interview-chevrolets-camaro-chief-on-track-simulation-models-mustang-rivalry/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=120</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Al Oppenheiser serves as General Motors' chief engineer for global rear-wheel-drive vehicles, and he's been having a very good year. We ranked him fourth in our annual Power List, and we named his freshly minted Camaro our <a href="http://www.motortrend.com/news/2016-chevrolet-camaro-is-the-motor-trend-car-of-the-year/" target="_blank"><strong>Car of the Year</strong></a>, proclaiming that it had graduated from the perpetual ponycar wars and was ready to take on Bavaria's best. Mr. O was in Chicago for the auto show <strong><a href="http://www.motortrend.com/news/2017-chevrolet-camaro-1le-first-look-review/" target="_blank">unveiling of his new 1LE packages</a></strong>, and Motor Trend sat down with him to ask what had gone so terribly right.
<div class="researchcars inline" data-aop="researchcars_articlepage_onecar_inline" data-id="76" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:76,&quot;p&quot;:54,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;vip-article-links&quot;,&quot;y&quot;:8,&quot;o&quot;:8}"><header><strong>We always loved the handling of the fifth-gen Z/28, but as cooking-grade Camaros go, the sixth gen seems to have made a quantum leap forward in chassis dynamics. How did the team manage that?</strong></header></div>
<div class="nativeAd show">
<div>
<div>Well, one of the benefits that we had is that the Alpha architecture was already established as a lightweight, structurally capable architecture. Of course a lot of things happened around 2009 at GM, and we were looking at scaling down the number of architectures we had from 17. Zeta is what the fifth-gen Camaro came off of, and to determine whether we used Zeta or Alpha for the sixth generation, we started looking at the attributes of the pure mass reduction that we needed—that you all told us we needed, and we all agreed—and decided that's just one thing that we need. We also needed to increase the bandwidth of that architecture. For instance, I need track width. I need tire [diameter] to help me win on the track. So I think we had the benefit of time to change some assumptions—to say we aren't just going to carry an Alpha ATS into a Camaro, we need to grow the bandwidth of that architecture to include a Camaro—a family of Camaros, including SS, V-6 1LE, V-8 1LEs, and you can dream beyond that. So I think, to your point, did we re-engineer everything? I think we had the benefit of time and had the ability to grow the Alpha bandwidth to be capable on the track, better than it was before.</div>
</div>
</div>
<strong>Were there new tools available that helped hone the fifth-gen dynamics?</strong>

Absolutely. We actually have the capability with our track simulation models to set up a car at Willow Springs and tell you from a laptop how it will perform, and we'll be [accurate] within a couple tenths of a second. That's the capability we have from a processing standpoint, from an aerodynamics iteration standpoint. We always throw out the term "9 million computational hours," and that's a big number, but it literally gives you the chance to run, 24 hours a day, computational models that take into account lift and drag, downforce, optimal setups—you can play with different settings on the computer. So if you think of going from the old days of build it, break it, fix it out at the proving grounds to doing things in the computer world, getting simulations that are realistic, we can have quick turnaround of parts and get them on cars quickly, and we can actually design a car on the computer that we can build and mirror track times almost identical.

<strong>That's 9 million computational hours just on the Camaro</strong><img title="Provided by MotorTrend" src="http://static-autos-wus.s-msn.com/sc/9b/e151e5.gif" alt="" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;wait&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq4D8D.img?h=373&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" />

<img class=" loaded" title="Provided by MotorTrend" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq4vnz.img?h=373&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="" width="562" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;wait&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq4vnz.img?h=373&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" />
<div class="inline-slideshow nonfullscreen clean">
<div class="gallery-container" data-aop="article" data-id="58" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:58,&quot;p&quot;:54,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;gallery&quot;,&quot;y&quot;:8,&quot;o&quot;:4}" data-fullscreen-url="/en-us/autos/news/interview-chevrolet%e2%80%99s-camaro-chief-on-track-simulation-models-mustang-rivalry/ss-BBq4Ioq?parent-title=interview-chevrolet%E2%80%99s-camaro-chief-on-track-simulation-models-mustang-rivalry&amp;parent-ns=ar&amp;parent-content-id=BBq4Ax6&amp;fullscreen=true" data-gallery-id="BBq4Ioq" data-page-id="galleryvnext" data-page-name="gallery_inline" data-page-provider-id="AA8DRt">
<div class="gallerydata" data-aop="article_slidedata">
<div class="show">
<div class="slidemetadata-container">
<div class="slide-metadata">Yes, that's 9 million computational hours on structural placement, on aerodynamic nannies that we added to the car, continually running iterations that crank out the optimal setting for ride height, and then that translates into spring rates.</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<strong>And you're also simulating the various modes of AdvanceTrac?</strong>

Absolutely. From the conservative Snow-Ice mode all the way up to everything off. So absolutely we can model all of that. We have this array that would blow your mind with how many rows and columns there are for all the different modeing, just for the production V-8 SS, with the different scenarios that happen with steering, with suspension, with performance traction management and what mode you're in. Then when you talk about a really track-focused car like the 1LE you add on the V-8 the [electronic limited-slip differential] and the MR [magnetic ride] shocks and those work together with the steering so that you can—in 150-millisecond increments, infinitesimal time—change the settings of the car as you're driving on the track. Those things allow us to really up our game in the corners.

<strong>Can you talk about spring rate changes and other specifics of the 1LE package?</strong>

We don't get into rates, but basically with the MR setup, and the stiffer suspension bits, the stabilizer bars, the cross-axis ball joint setup, the dampers, the inverted-tube MR suspension—it all works in concert with 1LE.

<span class="storyimage fullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" data-attrib="Provided by MotorTrend" data-caption="2017 Chevrolet Camaro 1LE rear end in motion" data-id="73" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:73,&quot;p&quot;:54,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:5}"><img class=" loaded" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq4vnf.img?h=484&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="2017 Chevrolet Camaro 1LE rear end in motion" width="728" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;73&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;48&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq4vnf.img?h=484&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size3column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq4vnf.img?h=415&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size2column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq4vnf.img?h=415&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" /></span></span>

We're looking at the strategy of sharing down components, so if you think of the V-8 1LE as the top dog of track performance—the largest bar diameter, the largest amount of front/rear downforce (of course all cars got the reduced rear roll-center height to help reduce rear squat much better than in the fifth generation)—so they all get that to start. Then comes the SS, and because we were planning to make a V-6 1LE all along, we were able to take our early development V-8 SS parts and throw them at the V-6 and do code development, so now you've got one set of springs, one set of dampers that work on the [V-8 SS and] V-6 1LE. Proliferating parts saves on development cost, it saves on development time, and when you plan it up front it's efficient all the way around.

<strong>Where does the 2.0-liter turbo fit in? Will customers be able to make a 2.0T 1LE?</strong>

At this point I'd tell you that the V-6 and the 2.0-liter turbo share a significant number of parts. So, could you do it? You could do it. Have we done it? We might have done it. I'm really excited about having the 2.0-liter in the lineup, because there was actually a segment of buyers that would not buy the fifth-gen because we did not have a 2.0-liter turbo. I call them the Fast &amp; Furious set. They did so much with our Stage kits from the EcoTec days that that's what they want. They want a lighter weight car, they want the 2.0-liter turbo, and we're offering one that does 0-to-60 in 5.4 seconds out of the gate, and I'm excited to see what they do with Stage kits, whether it's 40-horse up to 1,000-horse—the kits are out there—not our kits. But we've had them in the past, so they're familiar with that.

Our strategy with the Camaro has been to work closely with our Chevrolet Performance Parts team to create packages that can go across the non-performance models. So for instance, we're taking a look at, can we take the 1LE bits and offer them up to somebody who bought a car before the 1LE came out. This worked out really well toward the end of the fifth gen. It's already worked well on the sixth gen. Almost 60 percent of the cars that have sold since October's start of production have had at least one accessory ordered with them. So the fact that we had them ready to go from day one has been a success for us already in the sixth gen. So we're going to continue that strategy for sharing parts across all models, and the four-cylinder won't be excluded from that.

<span class="storyimage fullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" data-attrib="Provided by MotorTrend" data-caption="2017-Chevrolet-Camaro-ZL1-prototype-side1" data-id="74" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:74,&quot;p&quot;:54,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:6}"><img class=" loaded" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq4AwS.img?h=484&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="2017-Chevrolet-Camaro-ZL1-prototype-side1" width="728" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;73&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;48&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq4AwS.img?h=484&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size3column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq4AwS.img?h=415&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size2column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq4AwS.img?h=415&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" /></span></span>

<strong>I know you're not prepared to talk about future products, but are there any inherent stumbling blocks in the lighter, smaller Alpha architecture to offering up big-letter performance models like the ZL1 and Z/28?</strong>

You might see some big letters. You know this market. Ford's going to punch us, we're going to punch them—I can't wait until you do your 1LE versus GT350 comparison, maybe even the R comparison. But I'm sure they'll punch back. That's going to continue; that's the life blood. I think this is the golden age of Camaro versus Mustang. Is there a limitation? I'll tell you, with a guy like Reuss at the helm, we never have a limitation on what we want to look at. He'll never say "no." We just have to present something that's right for the car. I don't want to alienate previous customers because maybe we're shooting too far. Also we've got a pretty darned good performance lineup between Tadge [Corvette chief engineer Juechter] and I, between our entry 2.0-liter turbo Camaro and his top-dog Corvettes. I think that's unmatched in the industry, having two cars that can cover such a broad spectrum. But there's never a limitation, and we're never done pushing.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>120</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:23:21</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:23:21</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>interview-chevrolets-camaro-chief-on-track-simulation-models-mustang-rivalry</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="auto"><![CDATA[auto]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="autos"><![CDATA[Autos]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="interview"><![CDATA[Interview]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="travel"><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[240]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Zipcar Will Offer One-Way Trips in North America</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/zipcar-will-offer-one-way-trips-in-north-america/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=123</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[&nbsp;

Zipcar is looking to increase its offerings, and will now begin offering one-way trips in certain North American markets. Along with that, the company will also allow drivers to change destinations mid-trip and extend reservations indefinitely.

In 2014, Zipcar launched the One&gt;Way beta program in Boston, but now that the program will be transitioned into the new lineup of options, the company will change the name. The new one-way trip program will start out in Philadelphia, Denver, and Los Angeles on a small scale before getting rolled out in more cities. The Los Angeles program is set to launch in the coming weeks.

"We want to deliver to our customers before they even know they want it," said Zipcar spokeswoman Lindsay Wester to Automotive News. The addition of the one-way trip program, as well as the ability to change destination is part of Zipcar's strategy to adapt to customer demands. The new programs will let drivers drop vehicles off at different locations than where they picked them up, which will be a first for Zipcar.
<div class="nativeAd show"></div>
Currently, the company will only offer Honda vehicles like the Fit for the new flexible options. However, Wester said that Zipcar is "open" to adding other vehicles to its fleet as it continues to expand its driving options, which will later include travel between cities.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>123</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:25:50</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:25:50</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>zipcar-will-offer-one-way-trips-in-north-america</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="auto"><![CDATA[auto]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="autos"><![CDATA[Autos]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="sports"><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="travel"><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="travel"><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[238]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Bleak Picture of Great Barrier Reef’s Changing Chemistry</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/bleak-picture-of-great-barrier-reefs-changing-chemistry/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=125</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[As greenhouse gas pollution reshapes the invisible mosaic of seawater chemicals washing over Australia’s Great Barrier Reef, corals there are being locked in escalating conflicts with each other for survival.

A modeling-based study by Australian government scientists has tracked ocean acidification for the first time through all of the thousands of reefs comprising the psychedelic ecosystem, which is home to fish, sharks, dolphins and dugongs. The study was<a href="http://nature.com/articles/doi:10.1038/ncomms10732" target="_blank">published Tuesday</a> in Nature Communications.

<span class="storyimage smallfullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" style="box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0px auto; padding: 0px; cursor: pointer; display: block; line-height: 0; position: relative; background: #000000;" data-attrib="Provided by Climate Central" data-caption="The Great Barrier Reef is threatened by global warming, ocean acidification and pollution.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Credit: FarbenfroheWunderwelt/Flickr" data-id="50" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:50,&quot;p&quot;:47,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:3}"> </span></span>

<a href="http://wxshift.com/climate-change/climate-indicators/ocean-acidification" target="_blank">Ocean acidification</a> is caused by carbon dioxide pollution and it’s associated with a decline in calcium carbonate, which coral use to make their tough sheaths. That’s weakening coral reefs around the world, making them more vulnerable to impacts of ocean warming and water pollution.

The new findings suggest that the World Heritage site might not be able to withstand one of the more profound but lesser-known impacts of climate change.
<div class="inlineapppromo" data-aop="article-inlineapppromo_inlineapppromo" data-id="53" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:53,&quot;p&quot;:47,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;InlineAppPromoByCMS&quot;,&quot;y&quot;:8,&quot;o&quot;:6}"></div>
“While temperature is the near-term threat, acidification erodes the ability of corals and other calcifiers to keep pace with increasing numbers of extreme events,” said <a href="http://researchers.uq.edu.au/researcher/839" target="_blank">Ove Hoegh-Guldberg</a>, a marine science professor at the University of Queensland. He was not involved with the new study, which he described as solid. “The result is less and less coral.”

Ocean <a href="http://wxshift.com/news/ocean-acidification-real-time" target="_blank">pH has declined</a> to 8.1 from 8.2 since the Industrial Revolution, and while those are just numbers to most of us, “reef development is thought to cease at pH 7.8,” said <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/david-wachenfeld-449a06aa" target="_blank">David Wachenfeld</a>, director of reef recovery at the Great Barrier Reef Marine Park Authority, a government agency. He wasn’t involved with the study.

The new findings show that acidification inside the system of reefs is even worse than in the open oceans. That’s because corals in the outer reefs slurp up much of the calcium carbonate before it can reach the center.
<div class="imgright"><span class="storyimage smallfullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" style="box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0px auto; padding: 0px; cursor: pointer; display: block; line-height: 0; position: relative; background: #000000;" data-attrib="Provided by Climate Central" data-caption="A map of modeled ocean acidification impacts on the Great Barrier Reef. Stronger impacts are marked with darker blue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Credit: Mongin et al., The exposure of the Great Barrier Reef to ocean acidification, Nature Communications, 2016." data-id="51" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:51,&quot;p&quot;:47,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:4}"><img class=" loaded" style="box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0px auto; padding: 0px; border: 0px; max-width: 100%; cursor: pointer; display: block; line-height: 0; position: relative; width: 29rem; height: 40rem; background: #000000;" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpSgtc.img?h=400&amp;w=290&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="A map of modeled ocean acidification impacts on the Great Barrier Reef. Stronger impacts are marked with darker blue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Credit: Mongin et al., The exposure of the Great Barrier Reef to ocean acidification, Nature Communications, 2016." width="289" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;29&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;40&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpSgtc.img?h=400&amp;w=290&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" /></span></span></div>
<div class="imgright">

<span class="storyimage smallfullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="caption truncate" title="© Provided by Climate Central A map of modeled ocean acidification impacts on the Great Barrier Reef. Stronger impacts are marked with darker blue.Credit: Mongin et al., The exposure of the Great Barrier Reef to ocean acidification, Nature Communications, 2016."><span class="attribution">© Provided by Climate Central</span> A map of modeled ocean acidification impacts on the Great Barrier Reef. Stronger…</span></span>“It’s important that we understand how and where climate change, including ocean acidification, will impact the reef,” Wachenfeld said in an email. “It potentially allows us to take more targeted actions to build its resilience.”

</div>
By combining data from research sites with models, the researchers peered into the chemistry of the Great Barrier Reef, Earth’s <a href="http://www.gbrmpa.gov.au/about-the-reef/facts-about-the-great-barrier-reef" target="_blank">largest living structure</a>, which stretches nearly 1,500 miles.

“One of the things about the Great Barrier Reef is that there’s 3,500 reefs,” said<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/mathieu-mongin-6381a181" target="_blank"> Mathieu Mongin</a>, a marine biogeochemical modeler at the Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organisation (CSIRO) who led the new study. “We can’t measure it all. So we have to use models.”

The researchers discovered heavy salinity impacts in the heart of the system, with outer reefs gobbling up the declining supplies of calcium carbonate as it washes in from the Coral Sea.

The scientists concluded in the paper that their findings, combined with projected ongoing warming, show that even if rates of climate pollution are reigned in, that “may not be sufficient to avoid significant impacts” of acidification on coral reef regeneration.

That would lead to “potential losses in coral cover, ecosystem biodiversity and resilience,” the scientists wrote.

Although the findings were troubling, they’re being welcomed by other scientists.

“It’s always alarming to hear that things are going to get worse,” said <a href="http://ecoadapt.org/team/__details/paul" target="_blank">Paul Marshall</a>, a private industry scientist who previously led high-profile research into climate change’s impacts on the Great Barrier Reef. “But the paper provides insight that could be turned into action that can help build the resilience of reefs to these larger global stresses.”

The data provided a snapshot of current conditions. Next, the CSIRO scientists plans to model the future toll of worsening acidification throughout the Great Barrier Reef.

The future of the group that produced the paper is in question, however, making it unclear whether its plans for projecting future conditions at the reefs will move forward.
<div class="imgleft"><span class="storyimage smallfullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" style="box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0px auto; padding: 0px; cursor: pointer; display: block; line-height: 0; position: relative; background: #000000;" data-attrib="Provided by Climate Central" data-caption="Endangered hawksbill turtles are among seven species of marine turtles that can be found in the Great Barrier Reef.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Credit: Geir Friestad/Flickr" data-id="52" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:52,&quot;p&quot;:47,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:5}"><img class=" loaded" style="box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0px auto; padding: 0px; border: 0px; max-width: 100%; cursor: pointer; display: block; line-height: 0; position: relative; width: 72rem; height: 40rem; background: #000000;" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpS0gp.img?h=405&amp;w=720&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="Endangered hawksbill turtles are among seven species of marine turtles that can be found in the Great Barrier Reef.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Credit: Geir Friestad/Flickr" width="720" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;72&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;40&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpS0gp.img?h=405&amp;w=720&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size3column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;35&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpS0gp.img?h=351&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size2column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;35&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpS0gp.img?h=351&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" /></span></span></div>
<div class="imgleft">

<span class="storyimage smallfullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="caption truncate" title="© Provided by Climate Central Endangered hawksbill turtles are among seven species of marine turtles that can be found in the Great Barrier Reef.Credit: Geir Friestad/Flickr"><span class="attribution">© Provided by Climate Central</span> Endangered hawksbill turtles are among seven species of marine turtles that can be found in the Great Barrier…</span></span>The Australian government has announced that it plans to <a href="http://www.smh.com.au/environment/climate-change/csiro-planning-to-pare-back-share-climate-job-cuts-20160222-gn08w4.html" target="_blank">cut 90 or more jobs</a> from CSIRO’s ocean and atmosphere division, leaving <a href="http://www.smh.com.au/environment/climate-change/climate-will-be-all-gone-as-csiro-swings-jobs-axe-scientists-say-20160203-gml7jy.html" target="_blank">as few as 30 staff</a> remaining, though few details have been finalized or announced.

</div>
What’s clear, though, is that the future of the Great Barrier Reef will be shaped by how rapidly the world can transition from fossil fuels to cleaner sources of energy, which was the overarching goal of a <a href="http://www.climatecentral.org/news/world-unites-delivers-hopeful-climate-deal-19808" target="_blank">United Nations climate pact</a> agreed to in Paris in December.

Like other natural systems, the fate of the world’s reefs may be tied to the success of that treaty.

“This latest research serves to underline the fact that the single biggest thing we can do to protect the Reef for the future is to greatly reduce greenhouse gas emissions as soon as possible,” Wachenfeld said.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>125</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:28:43</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:28:43</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>bleak-picture-of-great-barrier-reefs-changing-chemistry</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="chemistry"><![CDATA[Chemistry]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="weather"><![CDATA[Weather]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[236]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Longest Global Coral Bleaching On Record Isn’t Over Yet</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/longest-global-coral-bleaching-on-record-isnt-over-yet/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=127</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Coral reefs have had a rough run over the past two years.

<a href="http://www.climatecentral.org/news/january-global-temperature-record-20035" target="_blank">Climate change</a> has ratcheted up ocean temperatures and <a href="http://www.climatecentral.org/news/one-graph-shows-el-ninos-new-record-19693" target="_blank">El Niño helped kick</a> them into overdrive in parts of the world. All that heat kicked off what has been a <a href="http://www.climatecentral.org/news/hot-oceans-global-coral-bleaching-19528" target="_blank">major coral die-off</a>around the globe.

&nbsp;

Coral bleaching alert levels over the past 30 days.

Credit: <a href="http://coralreefwatch.noaa.gov/satellite/bleaching5km/index.php" target="_blank">Coral Reef Watch</a>

While El Niño has <a href="http://www.climatecentral.org/news/el-nino-peaks-but-impacts-to-come-19900" target="_blank">passed its peak</a>, scientists have warned that the global coral die-off, known as coral bleaching, is still far from over. What began in 2014 is projected to continue through this year and even into early 2017.
<div class="inlineapppromo" data-aop="article-inlineapppromo_inlineapppromo" data-id="53" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:53,&quot;p&quot;:47,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;InlineAppPromoByCMS&quot;,&quot;y&quot;:8,&quot;o&quot;:6}">This is the third global bleaching event on record. The others were in 1998 and 2010, both El Niño years. El Niño, which is marked by warmer than normal waters in the tropical Pacific, has certainly played a role. The steady background creep of ocean warming due to climate change, however, is also an important factor. More than 90 percent of the accumulated heat due to climate change is <a href="http://www.climatecentral.org/news/global-warming-ocean-heat-18905" target="_blank">ending up in the oceans</a> and its effects are being acutely felt.</div>
“We are currently experiencing the longest global coral bleaching event ever observed,” Mark Eakin, the Coral Reef Watch coordinator, said in a statement.

The prolonged exposure to high water temperatures has left many reefs in critical shape. The warm water causes corals to expel the algae they rely on to grow, leaving ghostly white skeletons in the place of thriving coral communities.

<span class="storyimage smallfullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" style="box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0px auto; padding: 0px; cursor: pointer; display: block; line-height: 0; position: relative; background: #000000;" data-attrib="Provided by Climate Central" data-caption="&lt;p style=&quot;margin-bottom:1em;padding:0px 0.2em;font-size:13px;&quot;&gt;Coral bleaching forecast for March-June.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style=&quot;margin-bottom:1em;padding:0px 0.2em;font-size:13px;&quot;&gt;Credit:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coralreefwatch.noaa.gov/satellite/bleachingoutlook_cfs/outlook_cfs.php&quot; style=&quot;color:#0000aa;background-color:#92c0e0;&quot;&gt;Coral Reef Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;" data-id="51" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:51,&quot;p&quot;:47,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:4}"><img class=" loaded" style="box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0px auto; padding: 0px; border: 0px; max-width: 100%; cursor: pointer; display: block; line-height: 0; position: relative; width: 72rem; height: 26rem; background: #000000;" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpSTQk.img?h=263&amp;w=720&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="&lt;p style=&quot;margin-bottom:1em;padding:0px 0.2em;font-size:13px;&quot;&gt;Coral bleaching forecast for March-June.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style=&quot;margin-bottom:1em;padding:0px 0.2em;font-size:13px;&quot;&gt;Credit:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://coralreefwatch.noaa.gov/satellite/bleachingoutlook_cfs/outlook_cfs.php&quot; style=&quot;color:#0000aa;background-color:#92c0e0;&quot;&gt;Coral Reef Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;" width="720" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;72&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;26&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpSTQk.img?h=263&amp;w=720&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size3column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;23&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpSTQk.img?h=228&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size2column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;23&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpSTQk.img?h=228&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" /></span></span>

<span class="storyimage smallfullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="caption truncate"><span class="attribution">© Provided by Climate Central</span></span></span>

Coral bleaching forecast for March-June.

Credit: <a href="http://coralreefwatch.noaa.gov/satellite/bleachingoutlook_cfs/outlook_cfs.php" target="_blank">Coral Reef Watch</a>

&nbsp;
<div class="imgleft">

The Pacific Ocean has been the epicenter of the global bleaching event and Christmas Island has been the tiny bullseye of that epicenter. The 150 square mile island sits right in the middle of the El Niño-warmed waters.

</div>
Coral there have been subjected to some of the most stressful conditions anywhere in the world. Specifically, El Niño sent water temperatures as high as 88°F, or about 6°F above normal, in the region. That extended period of stress had already killed off a wide array of corals when <a href="http://shadow.eas.gatech.edu/~kcobb/" target="_blank">Kim Cobb</a>, a coral expert at Georgia Tech, <a href="http://www.climatecentral.org/news/coral-reefs-crystal-ball-climate-change-19762" target="_blank">visited the reef in November</a> during peak El Niño heat.

And though waters are cooling as <a href="http://www.climatecentral.org/news/one-graph-shows-el-ninos-new-record-19693" target="_blank">El Niño ebbs</a>, Cobb is expecting to see even more devastation when she returns to Christmas Island next month. She’s <a href="https://www.indiegogo.com/projects/an-el-nino-stress-test-for-corals--3#/" target="_blank">using crowdfunding</a> for the trip because of the rapid response nature of the work and the wealth of information she and other scientists can learn from.

<span class="storyimage smallfullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" style="box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0px auto; padding: 0px; cursor: pointer; display: block; line-height: 0; position: relative; background: #000000;" data-attrib="Provided by Climate Central" data-caption="&lt;p style=&quot;margin-bottom:1em;padding:0px 0.2em;font-size:13px;&quot;&gt;Airport Reef in American Samoa at the height of a bleaching event in February 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style=&quot;margin-bottom:1em;padding:0px 0.2em;font-size:13px;&quot;&gt;Credit:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.globalcoralbleaching.org/&quot; style=&quot;color:#0000aa;background-color:#92c0e0;&quot;&gt;XL Catlin Seaview Survey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;" data-id="52" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:52,&quot;p&quot;:47,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:5}"><img class=" loaded" style="box-sizing: border-box; margin: 0px auto; padding: 0px; border: 0px; max-width: 100%; cursor: pointer; display: block; line-height: 0; position: relative; width: 72rem; height: 31rem; background: #000000;" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpSxKp.img?h=309&amp;w=720&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&amp;x=268&amp;y=196" alt="&lt;p style=&quot;margin-bottom:1em;padding:0px 0.2em;font-size:13px;&quot;&gt;Airport Reef in American Samoa at the height of a bleaching event in February 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style=&quot;margin-bottom:1em;padding:0px 0.2em;font-size:13px;&quot;&gt;Credit:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.globalcoralbleaching.org/&quot; style=&quot;color:#0000aa;background-color:#92c0e0;&quot;&gt;XL Catlin Seaview Survey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;" width="720" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;72&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;31&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpSxKp.img?h=309&amp;w=720&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&amp;x=268&amp;y=196&quot;},&quot;size3column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;27&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpSxKp.img?h=268&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&amp;x=268&amp;y=196&quot;},&quot;size2column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;27&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpSxKp.img?h=268&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&amp;x=268&amp;y=196&quot;}}" /></span></span>

<span class="storyimage smallfullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="caption truncate"><span class="attribution">© Provided by Climate Central</span></span></span>

Airport Reef in American Samoa at the height of a bleaching event in February 2015.

Credit: <a href="http://www.globalcoralbleaching.org/" target="_blank">XL Catlin Seaview Survey</a>

&nbsp;
<div class="imgleft">

“I call it the data collection opportunity of an academic career,” she said. “How this reef evolved through this mega El Niño (represents) this incredible opportunity because we know we may face more extremes in the future.”

</div>
The data Cobb plans to collect will provide valuable insight into which corals survive this extreme heat event. With climate change expected to keep warming oceans, those types of insights could be <a href="http://www.climatecentral.org/news/super-el-nino-pacific-corals-19498" target="_blank">key to conservation efforts</a>, not just at Christmas Island but around the world.

And while Christmas Island should experience a reprieve with oceans returning to normal temperatures around the region later this year, other areas will continue to feel the heat. The odds are increasing for a La Niña event later this year. While that means cooler-than-normal waters for the eastern and central tropical Pacific, it ramps up temperatures in the western edge of the basin around Indonesia and the Papua New Guinea.

That area is known as the <a href="http://www.worldwildlife.org/places/coral-triangle" target="_blank">Coral Triangle</a>, an ecologically crucial spot for coral, fish, turtles and other sea creatures. It’s already under threat from the current global coral bleaching event and could face even higher risks if La Niña materializes.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>127</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:31:25</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:31:25</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>longest-global-coral-bleaching-on-record-isnt-over-yet</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="healthfitness"><![CDATA[Health&amp;Fitness]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="weather"><![CDATA[Weather]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[234]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Earth is warming 50x faster than when it comes out of an ice age</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/earth-is-warming-50x-faster-than-when-it-comes-out-of-an-ice-age/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=129</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Recently, <a href="http://www.theguardian.com/environment/2016/feb/08/sea-level-rise-could-last-twice-as-long-as-human-history" target="_blank">The Guardian reported</a> on a significant <a href="http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nclimate2923.html" target="_blank">new study published in Nature Climate Change</a>, finding that even if we meet our carbon reduction targets and stay below <a href="http://www.theguardian.com/environment/2015/dec/12/paris-climate-deal-key-points" target="_blank">the 2°C global warming threshold</a>, sea level rise will eventually inundate many major coastal cities around the world.
<blockquote class="quoted"><em>20% of the world’s population will eventually have to migrate away from coasts swamped by rising oceans. Cities including New York, London, Rio de Janeiro, Cairo, Calcutta, Jakarta and Shanghai would all be submerged.</em></blockquote>
The authors looked at past climate change events and model simulations of the future. They found a clear, strong relationship between the total amount of carbon pollution humans emit, and how far global sea levels will rise. The issue is that ice sheets melt quite slowly, but because carbon dioxide stays in the atmosphere for a long time, the eventual melting and associated sea level rise are effectively locked in.

As a result, the study authors found that due to the carbon pollution humans have emitted so far, we’ve committed the planet to an eventual sea level rise of 1.7 meters (5.5 feet). If we manage to stay within <a href="https://www.newscientist.com/article/dn17051-humanitys-carbon-budget-set-at-one-trillion-tonnes/" target="_blank">the 1 trillion ton carbon budget</a>, which we hope will keep the planet below 2°C warming above pre-industrial levels, sea levels will nevertheless rise a total of about 9 meters (30 feet). If we continue on a fossil fuel-heavy path, we could trigger a staggering eventual 50 meters (165 feet) of sea level rise.

Predicting how quickly sea levels will rise is a challenge. However, two other studies just published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences found that the <a href="http://www.realclimate.org/index.php/archives/2016/02/millennia-of-sea-level-change/" target="_blank">Antarctic ice sheet could melt more quickly than previously thought</a>, and thus contribute to relatively rapid sea level rise. Over the past century, <a href="http://www.realclimate.org/index.php/archives/2016/02/millennia-of-sea-level-change/" target="_blank">global sea level has risen faster than at any time in the past two millennia</a>, and most of the recent sea level rise is due to human-caused global warming. Several feet of sea level rise this century is likely, with a possibility of 5 feet or more.
<div class="inlineapppromo" data-aop="article-inlineapppromo_inlineapppromo" data-id="52" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:52,&quot;p&quot;:48,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;InlineAppPromoByCMS&quot;,&quot;y&quot;:8,&quot;o&quot;:4}"></div>
Sea level change during each of the twenty centuries of the Common Era. Illustration: Climate Central, based on Kopp et al. (2016), published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.

The Nature Climate Change study didn’t just look at sea level rise; it also looked at global temperature changes. <a href="http://globalwarmingart.com/wiki/File:Ice_Age_Temperature_Rev_png" target="_blank">Earth’s sharpest climate changes over the past half million years </a>have occurred when the planet transitions from a ‘glacial’ to ‘interglacial’ period, and vice-versa.

Right now we’re in a warm interglacial period, having come out of the last ice age (when<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Laurentide_Ice_Sheet" target="_blank">New York City and Chicago were under an ice sheet</a>) about 12,000 years ago. During that transition, the Earth’s average surface temperature warmed about 4°C, but that temperature rise occurred over a period of about 10,000 years.

In contrast, humans have caused nearly 1°C warming over the past 150 years, and we could trigger anywhere from another 1 to 4°C warming over the next 85 years, depending on how much more carbon we pump into the atmosphere.

What humans are in the process of doing to the climate makes the transition out of the last ice age look like a casual stroll through the park. We’re already warming the Earth about 20 times faster than during the ice age transition, and over the next century that rate could increase to 50 times faster or more. We’re in the process of destabilizing the global climate far more quickly than happens even in some of the most severe natural climate change events.

That rapid climate destabilization is what has climate scientists worried. It’s faster than many species can adapt to, and could therefore cause widespread extinctions, among other<a href="http://skepticalscience.com/climate-best-to-worst-case-scenarios.html" target="_blank">dangerous climate change consequences</a>. Coastal flooding in places like Florida has already become <a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2016/02/23/science/sea-level-rise-global-warming-climate-change.html" target="_blank">much more common than it was just 50 years ago</a>, and sea level rise is expected to keep accelerating.

As Aaron Goldner, one of the Nature Climate Change study authors told me, the next 10–20 years are critical in determining which path we follow. There’s a big difference between an eventual sea level rise of 1.7 meters and one of 9 meters.

The sooner we transition away from fossil fuels and cut our carbon pollution, the better we’ll be able to limit the climate destabilization and associated damages. It’s a sobering thought: our children, grandchildren, and future generations for hundreds, even thousands of years will feel the impacts of the choices we make over the next decade.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>129</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:34:05</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:34:05</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>earth-is-warming-50x-faster-than-when-it-comes-out-of-an-ice-age</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="global-warming"><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ice-age"><![CDATA[Ice Age]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="weather"><![CDATA[Weather]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[231]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>As a Volcano Awakens, Quito and Its Suburbs Get Ready</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/as-a-volcano-awakens-quito-and-its-suburbs-get-ready/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=131</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[A system set to develop across the central United States will trigger damaging thunderstorms and flooding downpours across the lower Mississippi Valley on the first day of March.

"The same storm that is raising concerns for winter weather across the Great Lakes and interior Northeast will bring a severe weather threat to the Deep South," AccuWeather Meteorologist Evan Duffey said.

Thunderstorms that first initiated over Oklahoma during Monday night will develop into a squall line on Tuesday.

A squall line is a continuous band of thunderstorms that can produce damaging wind gusts, flooding downpours and hail. Brief tornadoes are also possible along the leading edge of this line.
<div class="inlineapppromo" data-aop="article-inlineapppromo_inlineapppromo" data-id="52" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:52,&quot;p&quot;:48,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;InlineAppPromoByCMS&quot;,&quot;y&quot;:8,&quot;o&quot;:4}">"As is typical with many of these winter storms, the push of cold air clashing with the warm air in place will lead to a line of thunderstorms along the system's cold front," Duffey explained.</div>
Strong winds aloft can give the storms extra strength.

He added that localized damaging winds and brief flooding downpours would be the primary threats from these storms.

<strong>Strong Storms Target the Deep South</strong>

Cities that will likely be impacted by the squall line on Tuesday include Little Rock, Arkansas; Memphis and Nashville, Tennessee; and Shreveport, Louisiana. By Tuesday night, the line will shift into New Orleans, Knoxville, Tennessee, and Birmingham, Alabama.

While these storms will move through areas that were devastated by severe thunderstorms last week, it is highly unlikely that they will match the same intensity and magnitude. However, it only takes one tornado or damaging burst of wind to devastate a family and/or community.

Motorists should be aware of rapidly changing weather conditions should they encounter the squall line. Torrential downpours will lead to reduced visibility and excess water on roadways, which could disrupt the Tuesday evening commute.

Whether you are heading to the polls on Super Tuesday, walking between classes on campus or commuting to and from work, know exactly when severe thunderstorms will strike your location with AccuWeather MinuteCast®.

It is possible that a few locally heavy, gusty thunderstorms will reach as far to the northeast as parts of Kentucky, West Virginia and southern Ohio Tuesday afternoon.

As Tuesday night progresses, the storms will likely lose some of their punch once they reach Atlanta and the Appalachian Mountains.

Regardless, flash flooding and gusty winds will remain a concern until the storms exit the Southeast coast on Wednesday morning.

Behind this front, a brief spell of quieter and cooler weather is expected across the region before another round of rain and thunderstorms at late week.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>131</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:35:37</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:35:37</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>as-a-volcano-awakens-quito-and-its-suburbs-get-ready</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="volcano"><![CDATA[Volcano]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="weather"><![CDATA[Weather]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[264]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Alabama to be hub of scientific study of Southern tornadoes</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/alabama-to-be-hub-of-scientific-study-of-southern-tornadoes/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=133</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Lightning illuminates a house after a tornado touched down in Jefferson County, Ala., damaging several houses, Friday, Dec. 25, 2015, in Birmingham, Ala.ATLANTA — About 40 scientists from around the nation are expected to participate in "VORTEX Southeast," an upcoming study of the unique characteristics of tornadoes that develop in the South, weather researchers say.

ATLANTA — About 40 scientists from around the nation are expected to participate in "VORTEX Southeast," an upcoming study of the unique characteristics of tornadoes that develop in the South, weather researchers say.

Like earlier studies in the Midwest, the research based in Huntsville, Alabama, will include mobile radars, drones and other equipment that can measure tornado intensity. It is set to run through March and April.

VORTEX, an acronym for Verification of the Origins of Rotation in Tornadoes Experiment, began in the mid-1990s with a large tornado study that helped inspired the Hollywood film "Twister."

Another large study, VORTEX 2, took place from 2009-2010.
<div class="inlineapppromo" data-aop="article-inlineapppromo_inlineapppromo" data-id="52" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:52,&quot;p&quot;:48,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;InlineAppPromoByCMS&quot;,&quot;y&quot;:8,&quot;o&quot;:4}"></div>
This spring, researchers hope to learn more about the mysteries of Southern tornadoes, such as whether the landscape in the South gives them added power, and how to warn people at night, when many tornadoes strike in the South.

The research aims to find ways of better forecasting tornadoes, communicating warnings more effectively and finding out how the public responds to those warnings, according to documents from the National Severe Storms Laboratory, which is involved in the planning. The Norman, Oklahoma-based lab is part of the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration.

Unlike the original experiment, the latest iteration of the study will include several social scientists, who seek to learn more about how people respond to tornado threats in Southern states. They say they plan to conduct interviews with residents to probe the psychology behind tornado warnings and figure out ways to persuade people to take action when tornadoes are forecast.

It's human nature to seek "secondary confirmation" when tornado warnings are issued, but the nature of Southern tornadoes often prevents people from getting that, researchers say.

On the wide open plains in the Midwest, "people can just look out their window and see it coming from miles away and still have time to take action," said one of the researchers, Laura Myers, executive director of the Center for Advanced Public Safety at the University of Alabama.

That confirms the threat for them, prompting them to take cover.

But in the South, "we can't see them coming because of the terrain, the trees and they're often rain-wrapped," Myers said.

"We can't rely on that secondary confirmation," she said. "By the time we see it, it could be right on top of us."

So the question of how to satisfy people's psychological need for secondary confirmation is one focus of the research. Another is how to warn people at night, when many of the South's tornadoes tend to strike.

Michael Egnoto, an assistant clinical professor and researcher at the University of Maryland, has held focus groups in Tuscaloosa, Alabama; Lexington, Kentucky; and Winston-Salem, North Carolina.

"We've been working with meteorologists and they've been very, very open to the social science perspective," Egnoto said. "They're really excited about trying to understand the human factors and how that can positively impact outcomes: saving lives, reducing injuries and lowering the human and capital costs of storms."]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>133</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:37:20</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:37:20</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>alabama-to-be-hub-of-scientific-study-of-southern-tornadoes</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="weather"><![CDATA[Weather]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[262]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>How to protect pipes from freezing in frigid weather</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/how-to-protect-pipes-from-freezing-in-frigid-weather/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=135</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Winter's frigid air can bring with it possible plumbing problems, including frozen pipes.

"Frigid morning showers, frozen or cracked pipes, broken radiators, flooding, and leaks are just a few of the many unwanted plumbing issues brought on by cold winter weather," Horizons Services stated on their <a href="http://www.horizonservicesinc.com/reference/tips-articles/winter-plumbing-maintenance" target="_blank">website</a>.

&nbsp;

To avoid a potential mess and an expensive fix, here are some ways to prevent and protect pipes from freezing in cold weather.

<strong>Prevent clogged drains</strong>
<div class="inlineapppromo" data-aop="article-inlineapppromo_inlineapppromo" data-id="52" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:52,&quot;p&quot;:48,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;InlineAppPromoByCMS&quot;,&quot;y&quot;:8,&quot;o&quot;:4}"></div>
Treat sink and bathtub drains once a week with an environmentally friendly mix.

"Make up a mixture of 1 cup of salt, 1 cup of baking soda, and 1/4 cup cream of tartar. Pour equal amounts into your various drains and follow it with 2 cups of boiling water for each drain," as stated on the Horizons Services website.

<strong>Keep cabinets open</strong>

Opening cabinet doors in the kitchen and bathroom can help circulate warmer air around the plumbing, according to the <a href="http://www.redcross.org/prepare/disaster/winter-storm/preventing-thawing-frozen-pipes" target="_blank">American Red Cross</a>.

<strong>Let water drip from faucets</strong>

In frigid conditions, allow water to drip from a faucet served by exposed pipes, the American Red Cross suggests.

"Running water through the pipe - even at a trickle - helps prevent pipes from freezing," the Red Cross said.

<strong>Spread showers throughout the day</strong>

"At least 10-minute intervals between showers is optimal to maintain hot water and proper pressure," Horizons Services said. They also suggested turning up the water heater during the winter months. However, to prevent burns, do not set the temperature about 125 degrees Fahrenheit.

<strong>Keep thermostat at set temperature</strong>

While some might turn down the thermostat at night, the American Red Cross suggests that it is best to keep the temperature consistent during the day and night.

"By temporarily suspending the use of lower nighttime temperatures, you may incur a higher heating bill, but you can prevent a much more costly repair job if pipes freeze and burst," the Red Cross said.

<strong>Eliminate drafts </strong>

Check throughout the home for areas where water supply lines are located in unheated areas of the house.

"Take measures to prevent the flow of cold air in these areas," Horizon Services said.

Common unheated areas to check in your house include basements, attics, garages and under kitchen and bathroom cabinets.

"Both hot and cold water pipes in these areas should be insulated. A hot water supply line can freeze just as a cold water supply line can freeze if water is not running through the pipe and the water temperature becomes cold," Horizon Services added.

If a faucet or pipe ends up freezing inside the house, it can be thawed by using an electric hair dryer, wrapping an electric heat pad around the pipe or soaking towels in hot water and wrapping them around the frozen portion of the pipe(s). Make sure to <a href="https://www.allstate.com/catastrophe/pipes-freeze.aspx" target="_blank">start thawing closest to the faucet first</a> and that the faucet is turned on so that melted water can drip out.

In cases where the location of the frozen pipe cannot be located or it is not accessible, it is best to call a licensed plumber.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>135</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:46:30</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:46:30</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>how-to-protect-pipes-from-freezing-in-frigid-weather</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="weather"><![CDATA[Weather]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[260]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Justin Bieber Turns 22: Fans Wish Superstar A Happy Birthday!</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/justin-bieber-turns-22-fans-wish-superstar-a-happy-birthday/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=137</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://gossipcop.com/tag/justin-bieber" target="_blank"><strong>Justin Bieber</strong></a> turns 22 on Tuesday, and fans worldwide are wishing the superstar a very happy birthday.

“#HappyBirthdayJustin” actually began trending on Monday as the clock struck midnight across the globe. By Tuesday morning in the U.S., the trending topic changed to “#HappyBirthdayJustinBieber.” Thousands of tweets have been sent in honor of the birthday boy, with many Beliebers reflecting on his journey from a goofy but talented child star to a sexy heartthrob and internationally-respected musician.

&nbsp;

@ontariosbird wrote on Twitter, “So happy I’ve been here from the start what a journey watching Justin grow up.” @SecuteBelieber expressed, “happy birthday to the worlds best idol ever @justinbieber we all love you so much and we’re all proud of you.” And @justinudesx commented, “He was, is and will be the best thing that happened to me in adolescence and in my life #HappyBirthdayJustinBieber.”

“#HappyBirthdayJustinBieber this grammy award winning legend with 6 #1 albums,” said @thebionicbieber. @jdbdreamy pleaded with Bieber, “stop growing up please.” But @obrienpayno told fellow supporters, “don’t be sad because he’s growing, be happy because you’re growing with him.” Some fans have also posted pictures of themselves holding up birthday signs, and quite a few have shared then-and-now photos of the star through the years.

As <strong>Gossip Cop</strong> reported, Bieber got an early start celebrating his 22nd birthday over the weekend. The singer threw a huge party that drew everyone from Diddy and Joe Jonas to Hailey Baldwin and Kourtney Kardashian. No word yet on his plans for the big day, but there’s no doubt he’s feeling the birthday love from Beliebers everywhere.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>137</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:52:21</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:52:21</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>justin-bieber-turns-22-fans-wish-superstar-a-happy-birthday</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="entertainment"><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[258]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Will Smith Is All Smiles a Day After Getting Ribbed in Chris Rock&#039;s Oscar Monologue</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/will-smith-is-all-smiles-a-day-after-getting-ribbed-in-chris-rocks-oscar-monologue/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=139</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a class="celebdb" href="http://www.people.com/people/will_smith" target="_blank">Will Smith</a> isn't letting <a href="http://www.people.com/people/news/category/0,,personsTax:ChrisRock,00.html" target="_blank">Chris Rock</a>'s Oscar dig keep him down.

&nbsp;

Smith, 47, was all smiles as he was spotted leaving the set of his upcoming film <em>Collateral Beauty</em> in New York on Monday. There, he flashed his signature smile, signed autographs and snapped a few selfies with fans. At one point, he even threw up a peace sign for the photographers.

The actor's good mood comes just one day after Rock singled him and <a href="http://www.people.com/people/news/category/0,,personsTax:JadaPinkettSmith,00.html" target="_blank">Jada Pinkett Smith</a>out in his <a href="http://www.people.com/people/package/article/0,,20985752_20990559,00.html" target="_blank">opening monologue</a> at the awards ceremony.

While addressing the <a href="http://www.people.com/article/oscars-diversity-ceo-actors-members-speak-out" target="_blank">#OscarsSoWhite controversy</a>, Rock mentioned Smith and his wife, who decided to <a href="http://www.people.com/people/package/article/0,,20981907_20981372,00.html" target="_blank">skip the ceremony</a>.

"What happened this year? People went nuts. Spike [Lee] got mad. Jada went mad. Will went mad. Everyone went mad!" Rock said about the celebrities who spoke out on the matter. "Jada said she's not coming. I was like, 'Isn't she on TV show?' Jada's gonna boycott the Oscars? Jada boycotting the Oscars is like me boycotting Rihanna's panties – I wasn't invited!"

He continued: "Her man Will was not nominated for <em>Concussion</em>. I get it. You get mad. It's not fair that Will was this good and didn't get nominated. You're right. It's also not fair that Will was paid $20 million for <em>Wild Wild West</em>!"

<img class="loaded" title="&quot;If you want Black nominees every year, you need to have Black categories. That's what you need. You... - Mark Ralston/AFP/Getty" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq9PYW.img?h=373&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&amp;x=205&amp;y=85" alt="&quot;If you want Black nominees every year, you need to have Black categories. That's what you need. You already do it with men and women. Think about it. There's no real reason for a men and women category in acting. It's not track and field. You don't have to separate them. Robert De Niro never said, 'I better slow this acting down so Meryl Streep can catch up.' &quot;– Chris Rock, addressing #OscarsSoWhite in his opening monologue" width="280" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBq9PYW.img?h=373&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&amp;x=205&amp;y=85&quot;}" />

THE OSCARS MOST MEMORABLE QUOTES
<div class="inline-slideshow nonfullscreen clean">
<div class="gallery-container" data-aop="article" data-id="55" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:55,&quot;p&quot;:51,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;gallery&quot;,&quot;y&quot;:8,&quot;o&quot;:4}" data-fullscreen-url="/en-us/movies/oscars/from-kevins-serious-statement-to-goslings-quick-quip-the-shows-most-memorable-quotes/ss-BBq9V2k?parent-title=will-smith-is-all-smiles-a-day-after-getting-ribbed-in-chris-rocks-oscar-monologue&amp;parent-ns=ar&amp;parent-content-id=BBqcFIh&amp;fullscreen=true" data-gallery-id="BBq9V2k" data-page-id="galleryvnext" data-page-name="gallery_inline" data-page-provider-id="BBlOXnw">
<div class="gallerydata" data-aop="article_slidedata">
<div class="show">
<div class="body-text">
<div class="expand"><figure><figcaption>
<div class="caption">
<div>"If you want Black nominees every year, you need to have Black categories. That's what you need. You already do it with men and women. Think about it. There's no real reason for a men and women category in acting. It's not track and field. You don't have to separate them. Robert De Niro never said, 'I better slow this acting down so Meryl Streep can catch up.' "– Chris Rock, addressing #OscarsSoWhite in his opening monologue</div>
</div>
</figcaption></figure></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>139</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:54:27</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:54:27</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>will-smith-is-all-smiles-a-day-after-getting-ribbed-in-chris-rocks-oscar-monologue</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="entertainment"><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[256]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Constance Wu, Jeremy Lin and More Slam Chris Rock&#039;s Asian Joke at Oscars</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/constance-wu-jeremy-lin-and-more-slam-chris-rocks-asian-joke-at-oscars/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=141</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Although <a href="http://www.etonline.com/celebs/chris_rock/" target="_blank">Chris Rock </a>addressed <a href="http://www.etonline.com/awards/oscars/183396_chris_rock_opening_oscar_monologue_read_the_full_transcript/" target="_blank">diversity in Hollywood</a> head on during <a href="http://www.etonline.com/awards/oscars/" target="_blank">2016 Oscars</a>, many feel that his joke at the expense of Asians was a major misstep.

During the Sunday night award show, the 51-year-old comedian invited the accountants from PricewaterhouseCooper, who calculate the Academy voting results, to join him on stage.

Instead of actual employees, three young Asian children dressed in suits and carrying briefcases were brought on stage and introduced by Rock as Ming Zu, Bao Ling and David Moskowitz.

"If anybody's upset about that joke, just tweet about it on your phone that was also made by these kids," he said. The joke is believed to be a veiled reference to Asia child labor laws.

Following the sketch, many celebrities shared their distaste on Twitter.

"Seriously though, when is this going to change?!? Tired of it being 'cool' and 'ok' to bash Asians smh," Charlotte Hornets basketball pro Jeremy Lin wrote.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>141</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:55:21</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:55:21</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>constance-wu-jeremy-lin-and-more-slam-chris-rocks-asian-joke-at-oscars</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="entertainment"><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[254]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Foo Fighters breakup rumors are &#039;utterly ridiculous&#039;: rep</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/foo-fighters-breakup-rumors-are-utterly-ridiculous-rep/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=143</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[&nbsp;

Foo Fighters may be on a break and have no major announced projects planned for 2016, but that doesn't mean the group is headed for a split.

On Monday, the <em>New York Post</em>'s <a href="http://pagesix.com/2016/02/29/is-dave-grohl-going-solo/" target="_blank">Page Six</a> reported there's "tension" between band members Dave Grohl and Taylor Hawkins, citing an unnamed source, who claims Grohl is ramping up a solo career after<a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2016/02/28/oscars-2016-dave-grohl" target="_blank">performing</a> at the Oscars on Sunday. "The band is billing it as a 'break,' but it's totally Dave going solo and Taylor is pissed about it," the<em>Post</em>'s source said.

While a rep for the Foo Fighters declined comment to EW about Grohl's plans for 2016, the rep says any reports about the band breaking up are "utterly ridiculous."

The band has also said in recent interviews that they have no plans of calling it quits. When<a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2015/07/17/dave-grohl-interview" target="_blank">EW spoke to Grohl</a> last summer, he was adamant that the Foos would always be together. "The band is more than a musical group," he said. "It's a family and it's become a way of life with us. We love each other. When the Foo Fighters show up to the airport and there's four SUVs waiting to drive us away, we all get in one SUV, still, to this day. It's how we f--ing roll...We're not breaking up anytime soon, that would be like your grandparents getting a divorce. Too weird."

Hawkins, meanwhile, told <em><a href="http://www.billboard.com/articles/news/6890446/taylor-hawkins-foo-fighters-break-david-bowie-interview" target="_blank">Billboard</a></em> in February that the Foos have "nothing on the books" for this year and that he plans to focus on his cover band, Chevy Metal. "I just figure it's better to stay busy," he says. "None of us can sit around doing nothing."

The Foo Fighters wrapped up a 20th anniversary world tour last year; last fall, they surprise released the <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2015/11/23/foo-fighters-saint-cecilia-ep" target="_blank"><em>Saint Cecilia EP</em></a>. In a letter accompanying the release, Grohl explained the group would be taking some downtime.

"Maybe these songs are the bread crumbs that will help us find our way back when it's time," he <a href="http://www.rollingstone.com/music/news/foo-fighters-drop-surprise-free-ep-saint-cecilia-20151123" target="_blank">wrote</a>. "We could use a nice wander through the woods right about now. Another empty journal, another tap on the shoulder ... those things are never far behind. It's what lies ahead in those woods that excites me now.... So tonight, as I sit in my Berlin hotel room on our final tour for this album, counting down the days until we return home, I can't help but wonder when we will see each other again. Who knows? But, with everything Foo Fighter-related, it will only be when it feels right. And that's a feeling that's easy to feel."]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>143</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:56:47</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:56:47</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>foo-fighters-breakup-rumors-are-utterly-ridiculous-rep</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="entertainment"><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[252]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Jonah Hill is noticeably slimmer on New York film set</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/jonah-hill-is-noticeably-slimmer-on-new-york-film-set/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=145</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[&nbsp;
<div>

<a href="http://www.wonderwall.com/movies/Jonah-Hill-587.celebrity" target="_blank">Jonah Hill</a> is looking good!

The Academy Award nominee appeared noticeably thinner on the New York set of "Collateral Beauty" on Feb. 29.

The "21 Jump Street" star wore black slacks and shoes with a black sweater over a white collared shirt during the fashionable outing. He completed his look with a camel overcoat and stylish shades and sported a close-cropped 'do and a full beard.

It's unclear whether Jonah has turned over a new stylish leaf or was simply dressed in character for the film, which stars <a href="http://www.wonderwall.com/movies/Will-Smith-436.celebrity" target="_blank">Will Smith</a> as a New York advertising executive who experiences a personal tragedy that prompts him to retreat from his life. The A-list cast of the upcoming drama also includes Kate Winslet, Edward Norton, Keira Knightley, Helen Mirren, Michael Peña and Naomie Harris.

Jonah's size has yo-yoed several times in recent years.

The heavyset actor reportedly <a href="http://www.wonderwall.com/entertainment/pic-jonah-hill-debuts-super-skinny-look-after-losing-40-pounds-1630284.article" target="_blank">lost around 40 pounds</a> in 2011 for his role as an undercover cop in "21 Jump Street."

But by summer 2014, he'd begun to <a href="http://www.wonderwall.com/celebrity/profiles/bio/jonah-hill-587.article?photoId=166241" target="_blank">put the weight back on</a>.

There was definitely <a href="http://www.wonderwall.com/entertainment/jonah-hill-weight-gain-1854581.article" target="_blank">more of Jonah to love</a> in January 2015 when he was photographed wearing a colorful jacket on a New York film set.

In April, he looked <a href="http://www.wonderwall.com/entertainment/jonahhill-displays-shocking-weight-gain-on-the-set-of-arms-and-the-dudes-1869391.article" target="_blank">even bigger</a> on the Los Angeles set of his upcoming Todd Phillips-directed comedy "Arms and the Dudes," which co-stars Miles Teller. Jonah sported a light blue button-down shirt with khaki slacks and loafers in the shocking photos. (It's still unclear whether or not his role in the film necessitated the weight gain.)

But then the funnyman <a href="http://www.wonderwall.com/celebrity/profiles/bio/jonah-hill-587.article?photoId=174732" target="_blank">appeared slimmer</a> at the <a href="http://www.wonderwall.com/awards-events/golden-globes/2016-golden-globe-awards-red-carpet-33434.gallery" target="_blank">2016 Golden Globe Awards</a> on Jan. 10. He wore a black tuxedo with a bowtie during the awards ceremony, during which he presented an award with Channing Tatum.

And Jonah looked <a href="http://www.wonderwall.com/celebrity/profiles/bio/jonah-hill-587.article?photoId=176400" target="_blank">slimmer still</a> in all black at the Los Angeles premiere of "Hail, Caesar!" on Feb. 1.

The star addressed his weight during an interview with Vulture in 2011.

"Being healthier came along with maturity," he said. "And it's hard, because a lot of times people want you to be the guy you were when they met you. And I love doing funny movies, but I want to mature, literally, in how I treat myself. I'm not living in a frat house with a bong plastered to the table. ... But all this stuff [points to his body] is just part of maturing in body and in mind. I just want to be a good man and to make my family proud. And, you know, I want to live a long time."

</div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>145</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:58:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:58:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>jonah-hill-is-noticeably-slimmer-on-new-york-film-set</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="entertainment"><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[250]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Brad Pitt Moving Into Bachelor Pad Behind Angelina Jolie’s Back?</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/brad-pitt-moving-into-bachelor-pad-behind-angelina-jolies-back/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=147</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<strong><a href="http://www.gossipcop.com/tag/brad-pitt/" target="_blank">Brad Pitt</a></strong> is NOT moving into a bachelor pad in London without <strong><a href="http://www.gossipcop.com/tag/angelina-jolie/" target="_blank">Angelina Jolie</a></strong>’s knowledge, despite a fabricated tabloid report. <strong>Gossip Cop</strong> can exclusively bust this claim. We’re told it’s “ridiculous.”

Pitt is currently in the U.K. filming a movie, but according to <em><strong>OK!</strong></em>, the actor is looking to relocate there for good. A so-called “source” tell the tabloid that Pitt is “tired of staying in hotels” and supposedly “tried to convince [Jolie] that moving there together would be good for their marriage, but she refused to rearrange her schedule.”

&nbsp;

The magazine’s dubious insider then goes on to claim that Pitt is secretly shopping around for his own house in England and hasn’t told his wife. “Brad’s thinking time apart is exactly what they need,” alleges the tabloid’s “source.” But <strong>Gossip Cop</strong> checked in with an actual source close to the couple, who assures us that Pitt isn’t in the market for a supposed bachelor pad, and the tabloid’s story is simply “ridiculous.”

Of course, <strong>Gossip Cop</strong> isn’t surprised by the outlet’s phony report. We recently called out<em>OK!</em> for wrongly alleging that Jolie chose to shoot her upcoming movie in Cambodia merely as an excuse to get away from her husband. Only, Pitt accompanied Jolie to the country, along with their children, so the entire family could be together while she worked. The tabloid’s latest claim about Pitt’s nonexistent secret bachelor pad is equally untrue.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>147</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 19:59:30</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 19:59:30</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>brad-pitt-moving-into-bachelor-pad-behind-angelina-jolies-back</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="entertainment"><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[247]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Infantino: Russia and Qatar must deliver in 2018 and 2022</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/gianni-infantino-has-called-on-organizers-to-deliver-the-best-world-cups-in-history-in-2018-and-2022/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=149</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Gianni Infantino has called on organizers to deliver "the best World Cups in history" in 2018 and 2022.New FIFA president Gianni Infantino has dismissed the idea of the 2018 and 2022 World Cups being moved from Russia and Qatar respectively, and called on tournament organizers to deliver "the best World Cups in history."

New FIFA president Gianni Infantino has dismissed the idea of the 2018 and 2022 World Cups being moved from Russia and Qatar respectively, and called on tournament organizers to deliver "the best World Cups in history."

With the allocation of both tournaments under investigation by the FBI, there had been suggestions the bidding process could be re-opened to allow other countries the chance to stage football's showpiece event.

But Infantino, speaking on Monday during his first full working day in the job after winning Friday's election to succeed Sepp Blatter, has called for everyone to focus on ensuring the tournaments go without a hitch.

He told reporters in Zurich: "Concerning Qatar and Russia, the decisions were taken in 2010 by the executive committee, but since 2010 there has been speculation and allegations and noise. It's now necessary to organize the best World Cup in history in Russia in 2018 and in 2022 in Qatar."

In addition to Infantino's rise to power, FIFA also voted in a series of reforms on Friday in a bid to end the corruption which tainted the Blatter era.

One of them was the provision to reveal the salaries paid to senior officials, including Infantino. The Swiss said the issue of his remuneration had not been discussed as yet.

When asked what he would be paid, he said: "I have no idea yet. I know you can't believe it but it's not (for the) money that I was candidate to become FIFA president. I have not discussed with anyone about my pay or what my pay will be. We will see."]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>149</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:09:14</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:09:14</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>gianni-infantino-has-called-on-organizers-to-deliver-the-best-world-cups-in-history-in-2018-and-2022</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="sports"><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[150]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Keane: Premier League stars queuing up to join MLS</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/keane-premier-league-stars-queuing-up-to-join-mls/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=152</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="leading">Didier Drogba, Frank Lampard, Steven Gerrard, David Villa, Andrea Pirlo, Kaka, Ashley Cole and Nigel De Jong are all playing in MLS.</p>
<a href="http://www.goal.com/en-us/teams/usa/la-galaxy/2272?ICID=TA">LA Galaxy</a> captain <a href="http://www.goal.com/en-us/people/ireland/2120/robbie-keane?ICID=TP_TST_23">Robbie Keane</a> claims Premier League stars are "desperate" to make the move to MLS.

MLS has become home to some of the world's biggest starts since Keane followed David Beckham to Los Angeles in 2011, with Steven Gerrard, Frank Lampard, Andrea Pirlo, David Villa and Kaka among a host of high-profile players swapping Europe for the United States.

Former Premier League winners Ashley Cole and Nigel de Jong have also arrived in MLS, linking up with Keane at the Galaxy, while former Juventus attacker Sebastian Giovinco was last season's MLS MVP with Toronto FC.

Keane revealed players are now queuing up to get a taste of the USA's growing competition.

"There has been a massive difference between 2011 and now," the 35-year-old Republic of Ireland international told <em>Sky Sports</em>. "David Beckham was really the one who started it off and I followed him and since then, the influx of stars who have come over here has been absolutely huge. People like Kaka, Lampard, Stevie [Gerrard], [Giovani] Dos Santos, David Villa, Pirlo - they're massive, massive names in Europe.

"It's only going to get bigger and bigger, there's no doubt about that. The league is only going to get stronger. Players I've played with are calling me up now from England and Spain and are really, really desperate to come over here because they can see how much the league has grown and because of the lifestyle as well."

The Galaxy open their 2016 MLS season at home to D.C. United on Sunday, following Tuesday's CONCACAF Champions League quarterfinal return leg against Santos Laguna.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>152</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:12:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:12:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>keane-premier-league-stars-queuing-up-to-join-mls</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="sports"><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[153]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Wenger: Ozil, Sanchez deals not close</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/wenger-ozil-sanchez-deals-not-close/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=155</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="leading">Arsenal is not close to tying Mesut Ozil and Alexis Sanchez down to new contracts, but Arsene Wenger backed the latter to find form.</p>
Arsene Wenger has denied reports Arsenal is close to agreeing to new deals with star duo Mesut Ozil and Alexis Sanchez.

Ozil and Sanchez's contracts are set to expire in June 2018, but reports suggested the pair were nearing agreements to extend their stay at Emirates Stadium beyond that timeframe.

However, Wenger confessed there is nothing imminent on either player, saying: "No that's not close, no."

Sanchez has struggled for form since returning from a hamstring injury which sidelined him for nearly two months. However, the Arsenal coach is confident he will soon be back to his best.

"He's just coming back from injury. I believe that he's fighting to come back to his best," Wenger said. "His second half at Manchester United was quite positive and encouraging. We don't want him to lose confidence and continue to fight."

Arsenal faces Swansea City in the Premier League on Wednesday and goes into the game on the back of consecutive defeats to Barcelona and Manchester United. The nature of the 3-2 defeat at Old Trafford on Sunday drew criticism for Wenger, which he suggested was over the top.

"We were disappointed with the result but we've not had too much time to dwell on it and want to focus on the next game," he said. "It was an away game but now we have six home games and every one becomes very important.

"I'm never surprised by the criticism that comes, that's part of the media today. It's always a bit excessive and emotional but we have to deal with that and I don't complain about that. More and more people talk, but we won't listen to what people say and focus on what we do."]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>155</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:13:13</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:13:13</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>wenger-ozil-sanchez-deals-not-close</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="sports"><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[156]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Messi respects rival Ronaldo</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/messi-respects-rival-ronaldo/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=159</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="leading">Barcelona's Lionel Messi says Cristiano Ronaldo is a rival on the pitch but he respects the Real Madrid star.</p>
Barcelona star Lionel Messi insists there is a mutual respect between himself and Real Madrid's Cristiano Ronaldo.

Messi and Ronaldo are widely considered the best players of the modern era, with the debate over which of the two is the greatest splitting players, pundits and fans alike.

No player outside the superstar duo has won the Ballon d'Or since 2007 and the battle for number one, as well as their allegiance to Spanish football's rival superpowers, has led to rumors they dislike each other.

Argentina star Messi, though, has rejected those claims.

"We are professionals that defend our teams, and rivals in this game, nothing more than that," Messi told Argentine newspaper <em>El</em> <em>Grafico</em>. "Sometimes it happens that we win or that we lose. There has always been respect and nothing more."

Messi counts seven La Liga titles, three Copa del Reys and four Champions League winner's medals on his incredible list of achievements with Barcelona and he is also the club's record goal-scorer.

However, that has yet to translate to success on the international scene. Messi has been a losing finalist in the 2014 World Cup, as well as the 2007 and 2015 Copa Americas.

The 28-year-old has 49 international goals to his name and is closing in on Gabriel Batistuta's record of 57 for Argentina, but Messi insisted it is major honors not individual accolades that motivate him.

"I prefer to win something with the national team," he said. "I am not interested in records. They are there, but that does not make you win titles."]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>159</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:17:02</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:17:02</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>messi-respects-rival-ronaldo</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="sports"><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[160]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Zidane: Real Madrid has an attitude problem</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/zidane-real-madrid-has-an-attitude-problem/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=162</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="leading">The World Cup winner insists his side's defeat to Atletico Madrid on Saturday was not down to the fitness levels of his team.</p>
<a href="http://www.goal.com/en-us/people/france/1229/zinedine-zidane?ICID=TP">Zinedine Zidane</a> insists <a href="http://www.goal.com/en-us/teams/spain/124/real-madrid" target="_blank">Real Madrid’s</a> “attitude” was to blame for its derby defeat to <a href="http://www.goal.com/en-us/teams/spain/atl%C3%A9tico-madrid/2020?ICID=SP">Atletico Madrid</a>.

Defeat at the Santiago Bernabeu on Saturday has left Madrid 12 points behind La Liga leader Barcelona, with Zidane admitting that the title race is all but over.

The loss also sparked an outburst from Cristiano Ronaldo towards his teammates, but Zidane has dismissed claims that his players are not losing crucial key games due to a lack of conditioning.

“We're doing well physically,” said the Madrid boss. “For me, the defeat in the derby is not a question of fitness.

“That Atletico ran more than us is just data, for me we're doing well physically. It's other things."

Instead, Zidane pointed to individual matchups and his disappointment over not winning them.

“We have to win our battles. We lost a lot of battles. I see the team improving and we are still going to improve more, too," he said. “I don't know if I'm convincing you... Yes, it's an attitude problem. What we have to do is make sure it doesn't happen again.”]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>162</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:21:31</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:21:31</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>zidane-real-madrid-has-an-attitude-problem</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="sports"><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[163]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Guardiola: Gotze still important for Bayern</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/guardiola-gotze-still-important-for-bayern/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=165</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="leading">The former Borussia Dortmund wonderkid has seen injury restrict him to just seven league appearances this year, but his coach insists he remains a key part of the team.</p>
<a href="http://www.goal.com/en-us/people/germany/36456/mario-g%C3%B6tze?ICID=TP_TST_13">Mario Gotze</a> remains an important player for <a href="http://www.goal.com/en-us/teams/germany/bayern-m%C3%BCnchen/961?ICID=OP_TN_5_4_1">Bayern Munich</a>, according to <a href="http://www.goal.com/en-us/people/spain/3147/pep-guardiola?ICID=TP">Pep Guardiola</a>.

Gotze has made just seven Bundesliga appearances this season, only returning to the first team set-up late last month after a hamstring injury sustained in October.

The 23-year-old has been linked with a move away from the Allianz Arena, with Liverpool and Juventus reportedly interested in his signature.

Gotze has been an unused substitute in Bayern's last three fixtures and is not yet back to match fitness, but Guardiola feels he will have an influential role to play in the closing stages of the season.

"He needs more time, but he is getting better week after week. I have seven strikers," said the Spaniard. "[He is] very professional. He thinks about football 24 hours a day. We have another three months [of the season to go].

"We need all the players so that we can achieve our goals. He was, and is, important."

Bayern holds an eight-point lead over Borussia Dortmund – which it faces Saturday – at the Bundesliga summit, but Guardiola is solely focused on the club's encounter with Mainz on Wednesday.

"Everybody talks about Wolfsburg and Borussia Dortmund, but we are playing against Mainz. They are fifth in the league," he added. "Mainz have a great starting XI with many dynamic players and a really good goalkeeper."]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>165</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:23:47</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:23:47</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>guardiola-gotze-still-important-for-bayern</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="sports"><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[166]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>How a Plain, Large Living Room Transformed Into a Cozy, Multipurpose Space</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/how-a-plain-large-living-room-transformed-into-a-cozy-multipurpose-space/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=168</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Sometimes bigger isn’t better—especially when you’re not sure how to fill a space. That was the issue for interior designer Jaclyn Joslin of <a href="http://covetedhome.com/" target="_blank">Coveted Home</a>’s clients: a young family of four with a dog. “The biggest problem was the sheer size of the room,” Joslin says. “At the time, it just didn’t have enough furniture, making it feel even bigger. And despite its size, open layout, and large windows, it still felt really dark.”

Since the living room was the main space for the whole family, Joslin wanted to decorate with that in mind: “With two young boys and a dog, my main objective was to ensure that the space be both kid- and pet-friendly, and still remain comfortable and stylish,” she says. “As the main hub of the home, it serves many purposes from entertaining guests to housing toys.”

To start, she added custom built-ins on each side of the fireplace. “This made a huge impact on the overall look,” she says. “Originally, these walls were blank and made the room feel very empty. Now there’s plenty of storage and spots to display collectibles, which is key for a multipurpose, kid-friendly space.” Then Joslin added some fresh color—Farrow &amp; Ball’s Pale Powder for the walls and Light Blue for the built-ins—to brighten the space. Joslin also brought in more furniture to scale for the size of the room: two large sofas, two plush armchairs, accent tables, and a large ottoman.

To create a cozy, livable space in any expansive room, Joslin says: “Start by anchoring the space with a rug and opt for furniture that is plush and comfortable, which adds a cozy element.” To define and anchor the seating area even more, she placed accent tables strategically in the room, like the console table behind the sofa, which acts as a border. “Finally, add personality,” she says. “We displayed personal mementos in the bookshelves and hung beautiful art pieces.”

And even though the space looks stylish now, it’s still a livable room for two young kids and a dog. “There’s no need to sacrifice style to make a space kid-friendly,” Joslin says. “Opt for furniture and accessories in darker colors to keep them from showing stains. Always choose durable fabrics for upholstered furniture, so that they hold up to wear and tear and are easy to clean. Lastly, think about sharp corners—the tufted ottoman in this room was chosen in place of a coffee table for this very reason.”]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>168</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:32:01</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:32:01</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>how-a-plain-large-living-room-transformed-into-a-cozy-multipurpose-space</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[169]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>How to Turn an Ikea Coffee Table Into the Bedroom Bench of Your Dreams</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/how-to-turn-an-ikea-coffee-table-into-the-bedroom-bench-of-your-dreams/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=171</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<em>With this simple hack, Jess Blazejewski of <a href="http://www.stylemepretty.com/living/2015/09/11/diy-coffee-table-bench/" target="_blank">Style Me Pretty Living</a> shows us how to turn an inexpensive coffee table into a gorgeous luxe bench.</em>

This bench was actually repurposed from a $60 coffee table! We painted the legs gold, then wrapped a piece of velvet like fabric over a precut piece of foam using nothing more than a staple gun. Boom, done! I am a little in love with this project and feel like of all of our ideas, this one really feels the most luxe, the most high end.

Materials

<a href="http://www.ikea.com/us/en/catalog/products/80303442/" target="_blank">Ikea coffee table</a>

Gold spray paint

1 yard fabric

1 1/4 yards of 2″ thick, 24″ wide foam sheet

Yardstick

Sharpie

Scissors

Pliers

Staple gun

1/4″ staples

Costs and time: $100 per bench (plus some tools from around the house - scissors, pliers, staple gun)

1 1/2 hrs. per bench

Instructions

1. Use pliers to twist off the metal tabs on the bottom of the long table. Pull them straight up and straight down a few times and they should pop right off.

2. Spraypaint the frame of the table gold and let dry 1 hour.

3. Trace the composite board of the coffee table with the sharpie on the foam sheet. Cut out the foam sheet along the lines with a bread knife.

4. Cut the fabric to be 8″ wider and longer than the table base.

5. Layer the foam sheet, then fabric, on top of the base. Staple gun the fabric to the underside of the base to secure it. At corners, fold the fabric to make a nice seam and then staple.

6. Place the base on the top of the gold frame and your bench is ready to go!]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>171</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:34:38</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:34:38</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>how-to-turn-an-ikea-coffee-table-into-the-bedroom-bench-of-your-dreams</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[172]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Style Your Home for Spring: 12 Easy Decorating Tricks</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/style-your-home-for-spring-12-easy-decorating-tricks/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:36:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=174</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>BRANCH OUT</h2>
<figure><figcaption>
<div class="caption">
<div>Vases aren’t just for <a href="http://www.rd.com/home/decorating/how-to-make-flowers-last-longer/" target="_blank">flowers</a>: Cut a branch or two from plants in your yard and place in a vase with water. 'A sculptural branch off a bush or tree makes for an unexpected and delightful connection with the outdoors,' says <a href="http://www.sarahbarnard.com/" target="_blank">Sarah Barnard</a>, LEED AP, an interior designer in Los Angeles. 'Whatever is growing at the moment gets to be on your foyer table, and it costs nothing.' A go-to choice is a cherry blossom branch, but virtually any branch will work—experiment with jade, eucalyptus, or any other plant in your yard.</div>
<div><img src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpG3wW.img?h=373&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="Brighten your &lt;a href='http://www.rd.com/food/recipes-cooking/kitchen-hacks/'&gt;kitchen&lt;/a&gt; with a pop of &lt;a href='http://www.rd.com/home/cleaning-organizing/34-reasons-to-load-up-on-lemons/'&gt;yellow&lt;/a&gt;. Fill a white bowl or glass vase with lemons for sunny functionality. Not only are lemons inexpensive décor—they’re convenient to have on hand for whipping up, say, a fresh spring salad. Yellow daffodils also illuminate a room." /></div>
</div>
</figcaption></figure>
<h2>SHOWCASE LEMONS</h2>
<figure><figcaption>
<div class="caption">
<div>Brighten your <a href="http://www.rd.com/food/recipes-cooking/kitchen-hacks/" target="_blank">kitchen</a> with a pop of <a href="http://www.rd.com/home/cleaning-organizing/34-reasons-to-load-up-on-lemons/" target="_blank">yellow</a>. Fill a white bowl or glass vase with lemons for sunny functionality. Not only are lemons inexpensive décor—they’re convenient to have on hand for whipping up, say, a fresh spring salad. Yellow daffodils also illuminate a room.</div>
</div>
</figcaption></figure>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>174</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:36:32</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:36:32</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>style-your-home-for-spring-12-easy-decorating-tricks</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[175]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Clever Way to Reach Dust in Hard-to-Reach Places</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/the-clever-way-to-reach-dust-in-hard-to-reach-places/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=178</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Ugh, that dust bunny <em>alllll</em> the way under your dresser has been eluding you for days. If only you could reach it… News flash! You can! Here’s what you do.

<strong>What you need:</strong> A pair of stockings and a broom.

<strong>What you do:</strong> Wrap the legwear around the head of the broom and use the long handle as leverage to pinpoint dust around door trims, crown molding and under pieces of furniture.

<strong>Why it works:</strong> The static cling attracts dust like a magnet.

<strong>Can I reuse the tights? </strong>Totally! Just wash them first.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>178</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:37:19</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:37:19</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>the-clever-way-to-reach-dust-in-hard-to-reach-places</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[179]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>How to Set Up a Smart Home</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/how-to-set-up-a-smart-home/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=181</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[When professional home builders Lindsay and Matthew Thomas of Thomas Development and Construction decided to build their family <a href="http://www.architecturaldigest.com/story/gil-schafer-farmhouse-article?mbid=synd_msnlife" target="_blank">farmhouse</a>, they knew they wanted to use innovative, energy-saving technology to automate their daily activities without cords or wires cluttering up the design—the interiors would be as minimalist as the clean-lined architecture. The solution: wiring the walls for a home automation system that conceals everything from the A/V cables to the television remote and makes it all operable with the touch of a tablet screen—if it hasn’t already learned your habits. Here, Lindsay Thomas shares the couple’s tried-and-true advice for creating your very own <a href="http://www.architecturaldigest.com/gallery/8-new-smart-home-products-unveiled-ces?mbid=synd_msnlife" target="_blank">smart home</a>.

<strong>Find a smart-home specialist. </strong>While you could try to tackle home automation on your own, Thomas recommends turning to an expert from a company that uses this technology every day, such as <a href="http://www.rticorp.com/?mbid=synd_msnlife" target="_blank">RTI</a>. By working with a professional, along with other important players—your HVAC technician, electrician, and pool company, for example—you can integrate your existing systems, including your music, lighting, TV, thermostat, motorized shades, and security alarms, so all are easily operable from one program or device. Ask about technology that is capable of changing the environment based on the occupant’s likes and dislikes. At the Thomas residence, “it can adjust lighting levels. It can determine that this person likes the bedroom temperature at 75 degrees, while this other person likes it cooler,” Thomas says. “It knows if you like to listen to music when you come home at night, or it can turn on a particular television show you watch.”

<strong>Wire everything at once. </strong>If you’re building a new home, have your builder and specialist add structure wiring to the floor plan from the beginning. Mark spots for audio, video, cable, security systems, and anything else you might want down the road. “Leave yourself every option for future needs,” says Thomas. Having the wiring mapped out is just as important when updating an existing residence—you don’t want to end up with a bunch of unnecessary holes in the walls.

<strong>Use just one device. </strong>“True home automation is all operated from one device,” says Thomas. “Using five different apps isn’t the same thing as integration automation through a single interface.” At her farmhouse, everything—the DVD players, alarm system, garage doors, and powered insect screens outside—is controlled through an iPad.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>181</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:40:30</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:40:30</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>how-to-set-up-a-smart-home</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[182]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Advanced Relapsing-Remitting MS: Comparing Latest Treatment Options</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/advanced-relapsing-remitting-ms-comparing-latest-treatment-options/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=184</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (RRMS) treatment has come a long way in recent years. Combining drug therapy with natural and alternative treatments can help manage symptoms, reduce the number of relapses, and slow disease progression.

Understanding your options can help you and your doctor choose the treatment that’s right for you.
<h2>Medications for RRMS</h2>
Currently, there are 12 medications approved by the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) for treating RRMS. Some of these medications are specifically for the treatment of advanced RRMS that hasn’t responded to other treatments. They include:
<ul>
	<li><strong>Aubagio</strong><strong> (teriflunomide):</strong> This drug is taken daily by mouth for the treatment of relapsing forms of MS.</li>
	<li><strong>Avonex</strong> <strong>(interferon beta-1a):</strong> Avonex prevents the immune system from attacking the central nervous system, reducing the frequency and severity of attacks. It’s injected into the muscle once a week or under the skin three times a week for the treatment of RRMS.</li>
	<li><strong>Betaseron</strong><strong> (interferon beta-1b):</strong> This medication is made from human blood plasma and given by injection under the skin every other day to reduce the number and severity of relapses and inflammation.</li>
	<li><strong>Copaxone</strong><strong> (glatiramer acetate):</strong> This biological drug is made from four different proteins. Copaxone can be given daily or at a higher dose every three days via an injection under the skin.</li>
	<li><strong>Extavia (</strong><strong>interferon beta-1b</strong><strong>):</strong> This drug is given every other day via injection under the skin to reduce symptoms and the number of RRMS attacks.</li>
	<li><strong>Gilenya</strong><strong> (fingolimod):</strong> Taken orally every day, Gilenya works to reduce the number of attacks and delay disability.</li>
	<li><strong>Lemtrada (alemtuzumab):</strong> The FDA recommends that this medication be reserved for those who haven’t had a good response to one or two other drugs. It’s given intravenously for five consecutive days for one year and then three consecutive days beyond that.</li>
	<li><strong>Novantrone</strong><strong> (mitoxantrone):</strong> Commonly used to treat cancer, Novatrone is given intravenously four times a year under the supervision of a doctor. The <a href="http://www.nationalmssociety.org/" target="_blank">National MS Society</a> advises not to exceed 8 to 12 doses over two to three years.</li>
	<li><strong>Plegridy</strong><strong> (pegylated interferon beta-1a):</strong> Unlike other interferons, Plegridy stays active in the body for longer periods. It’s given every two weeks to reduce relapses and brain lesions and delay physical disability.</li>
	<li><strong>Rebif (</strong><strong>interferon beta-1a</strong><strong>):</strong> This drug is given by injection under the skin three times a week and works similar to Avonex.</li>
	<li><strong>Tecfidera</strong> <strong>(dimethyl fumarate):</strong> Approved for treatment of RRMS in 2013 and formerly known as BG-12, Tecfidera is taken orally twice a day in 120 mg capsules for one week and 240 mg beyond that.</li>
	<li><strong>Tysabri (</strong><strong>natalizumab</strong><strong>):</strong> According to the <a href="http://www.nationalmssociety.org/" target="_blank">National MS Society</a>, this drug shouldn’t be used in combination with any of the other disease-modifying drugs (DMDs) for MS. It’s recommended for those who’ve not seen improvement with other medications. Ask your doctor about a referral because it requires special administration procedures.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Medications to Treat the Symptoms of RRMS</h2>
Other medications are available to help you get relief from the symptoms of RRMS. Your doctor can prescribe a muscle relaxant to help with stiffness and spasms. There are also medications available to treat fatigue, pain, sexual dysfunction, as well as bladder and bowel issues.
<h2>Complementary Treatments for RRMS</h2>
Although treatment with an FDA-approved DMD is recommended, there are complementary lifestyle treatments that you can use alongside medication to help manage the symptoms of RRMS.
<h3>Physical Therapy</h3>
A physical therapist can teach you different exercises to help stretch and strengthen muscles, which may reduce pain and make it easier for you to perform your daily activities. MS can cause muscle weakness so it’s important to try to maintain strength.
<h3>Exercise</h3>
Various <a href="http://nnr.sagepub.com/content/23/2/108.abstract" target="_blank">studies</a> have found that exercise can improve walking mobility in those with MS. Exercise can also improve cardiovascular function and strength, bladder and bowel function, combat fatigue, and fight depression. Walking, yoga, and adaptive tai chi are just a few types of exercise recommended for those with RRMS.
<h3>Acupuncture</h3>
Although there’s no current evidence to suggest that acupuncture can reduce the number of attacks or slow disease progression, the <a href="http://www.nationalmssociety.org/Treating-MS/Complementary-Alternative-Medicines/Acupuncture" target="_blank">National MS Society</a> suggests that it may provide relief for some of the symptoms of MS, including:
<ul>
	<li>pain</li>
	<li>numbness</li>
	<li>spasticity</li>
	<li>depression</li>
	<li>bladder issues</li>
</ul>
Having RRMS is difficult, and managing your condition may take some trial and error. But by working with your doctor and being open about your symptoms, you can find a medication and treatment approach that’s right for you.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>184</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:50:12</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:50:12</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>advanced-relapsing-remitting-ms-comparing-latest-treatment-options</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[185]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>What Happened When a Regular Guy Decided to Live Like &#039;The Rock&#039;</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/what-happened-when-a-regular-guy-decided-to-live-like-the-rock/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=187</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Most people looking to spice up their life a bit would go on vacation, try out a new hobby or get a haircut. Not Mark Webster. Instead, he looked to Dwayne “The Rock” Johnson for inspiration.

Webster, a 37-year-old startup founder living in New York City, decided to create Rock’ing for 30 Days, a monthlong challenge where he follows The Rock’s eating and exercising plan verbatim. That means spending about two hours a day, six days a week, in the gym doing cardio training and weightlifting, as well as eating exactly the same amount of food the six foot, five inch, 260-pound former professional wrestler gobbles down each and every day.

The Rock’s diet has been well-documented over the years on the movie star’s Instagram page, as well as in interviews with fitness websites. Webster collected all the information he could on how much Johnson eats, and the numbers are pretty staggering. Over the course of the day, Webster found The Rock eats seven meals for a total of 5,165 calories, 566 grams of carbohydrates, 109 grams of fat, and 460 grams of protein. That’s nearly three times the amount the USDA recommends for the average male. The most interesting aspect of The Rock’s diet is his consumption of cod. Johnson eats about 2.3 pounds of the fish<em>each day</em>, which stat-site FiveThirtyEight calculated to mean he spends about $1,400 a year on cod alone.

As for gym time, The Rock spends about 50 minutes each workout on the elliptical before hitting the weights for upwards of 90 minutes. Webster found Johnson’s training plan looked something like this:
<ul>
	<li>Monday: 50 minutes elliptical, chest workout</li>
	<li>Tuesday: 50 minutes elliptical, legs workout</li>
	<li>Wednesday: 50 minutes elliptical, arms workout</li>
	<li>Thursday: 50 minutes elliptical, back workout</li>
	<li>Friday: 50 minutes elliptical, shoulders workout</li>
	<li>Saturday: 50 minutes elliptical, legs workout</li>
	<li>Sunday: Rest</li>
</ul>
In a recent Reddit post, Webster said he was about halfway through the challenge, and had learned a few tidbits thus far. The hardest part of the whole endeavor was the meal prep. "All in all, it takes about an hour and fifteen minutes to do all the prep," Webster told <em>Tech Insider</em>. "My kitchen becomes like a little cafeteria." Eating like The People’s Champ doesn’t come cheap either: Webster said he spends about $42 per day on himself, rocketing his food costs over the course of the month up to around $1,200.

Webster said ingesting more than 5,000 calories each day hasn’t affected his weight at all. He’s noticed his abs and shoulders are a bit more defined, and his midsection feels flatter and wider. He said he feels great, even after going through a grueling eating and exercising regimen. Webster said he’ll end the pace of his challenge at the end of the 30 days, but will still take the things he learned, like how important nutrition is to exercise, with him as he goes back to leading a normal life. He also said he’ll never eat cod again.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>187</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:57:06</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:57:06</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>what-happened-when-a-regular-guy-decided-to-live-like-the-rock</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="healthfitness"><![CDATA[Health&amp;Fitness]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[188]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>20 Unwritten Gym Rules You Must Follow</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/20-unwritten-gym-rules-you-must-follow/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 20:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=190</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>SHOW SOME RESPECT</h2>
<figure><figcaption>
<div class="caption">
<div>

For many, the gym is considered to be a destination of sanctity and peace. A place where we can forget the headaches of the world and become one with the iron. Whether you consider the gym to be a place of worship where you pray for the gains you are about to receive, or a social necessity where you hit the bar on a daily basis, there are certain unwritten rules that must be followed for the well-being of all those in attendance.

The gym is a generally a great atmosphere for all those to enjoy if the proper rules and protocol are followed. Keep these simple guidelines in mind at all times before stepping foot onto the gym floor.

</div>
</div>
</figcaption></figure>
<h2>WIPE IT DOWN</h2>
<figure><figcaption>
<div class="caption">
<div>

After performing numerous sets the bench is bound to be covered in sweat, blood, and maybe even tears. Do the next guy a favor and pay it forward by wiping that thing down after use.

</div>
</div>
</figcaption></figure>
<h2>WALK AWAY</h2>
<figure><figcaption>
<div class="caption">
<div>

If there is some type of object sitting on or around a piece of equipment this is the international symbol for, "hey bro, this is taken." The individual has either a) gone to another area of the gym to do a superset, b) is getting water, or c) is using the restroom. Regardless of the reason, follow the code and don’t use the equipment.

</div>
</div>
</figcaption></figure>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>190</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 20:58:53</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 20:58:53</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>20-unwritten-gym-rules-you-must-follow</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="healthfitness"><![CDATA[Health&amp;Fitness]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[191]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Best Running Gear for All Levels</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/the-best-running-gear-for-all-levels/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=193</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>1. WATCH</h2>
<figure><figcaption>
<div class="caption">
<div>

The Forerunner® 630 by <a href="https://buy.garmin.com/en-US/US/into-sports/running/forerunner-630/prod516105.html" target="_blank">GARMIN</a> is the ultimate runners <a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/10-best-gps-watches-runners-slideshow" target="_blank">watch</a>. It is a GPS smartwatch with <a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/fitness/gear/how-accurate-your-fitness-tracker" target="_blank">advanced</a>running metric. It has a touch screen and high resolution color display for when you’re running at night. The Forerunner® 630 tracks your stride length and ground contact time balance while also allowing you to share on social media and control your music. Get it today for $399.99.

</div>
</div>
</figcaption></figure>
<h2>2. HEADBANDS</h2>
<figure><figcaption>
<div class="caption">
<div>

Ladies, we know how annoying it is, <a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/18-ways-change-your-running-routine" target="_blank">running</a> with our hair in our face. Sparkly Wide Headbands by <a href="http://shop.sparklysoul.com/Sparkly-Large-Headband_c3.htm" target="_blank">SPARKLY SOUL</a> is the perfect solution. They are 5/8 of an inch wide, nonslip, and won’t snag on your hair. These headbands come in a variety of colors; some even have sparkles and designs. Buy one today for only $17.00.
<h2>3. NUTRITION</h2>
<figure><figcaption>
<div class="caption">
<div>

Everyone knows running how important it is to feel energized before a run. Power Bar <a href="http://shop.powerbar.com/PowerBar-Energy-Blasts--Variety-15Pack/p/PWR-VPBLAST15&amp;c=PowerBar@EnergyBlasts" target="_blank">Energy Blasts™ Variety 15-Pack</a> ($22.85) are the perfect solution for you. Power Bar’s Energy Blasts are great tasting chews that provide your muscles the energy they need so you can <a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/top-10-super-foods-runners" target="_blank">run</a> that extra mile.

</div>
</div>
</figcaption></figure></div>
</div>
</figcaption></figure>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>193</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 21:02:08</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 21:02:08</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>the-best-running-gear-for-all-levels</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="healthfitness"><![CDATA[Health&amp;Fitness]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[194]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>How to Get in Shape Just By Walking</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/how-to-get-in-shape-just-by-walking/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=196</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Here is some good news for people who <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/5-workouts-people-who-hate-exercise" target="_blank">don’t like</a></strong> to work out. You’re doing it every time you walk. Nobody thinks of this <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/could-aerobic-exercise-slow-growth-cancerous-tumors" target="_blank">aerobic activity</a></strong> as an exercise because more than 7 billion people do it daily and it’s not hard. So how could something so easy, <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/race-walking-low-impact-sport-high-impact-gains" target="_blank">low-impact</a></strong>, simple, accessible and, for the most part, <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/fitness/n/6-signs-you-are-addicted-exercise-or-are-close-getting-there" target="_blank">enjoyable</a></strong> actually be good for us?

No amount of walking will help you <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/fitness/n/how-long-does-it-take-get-out-shape" target="_blank">get in shape</a></strong>unless you change your diet from <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/expert-advice-fighting-stress-induced-junk-food-cravings" target="_blank">junk</a></strong> to healthy food. Once you make that wise choice, the rest will follow. A <strong><a href="http://www.icr.org/article/humans-were-made-for-walking/" target="_blank">study</a></strong> from the University of Utah basically proved that people are made to walk. Researchers had different athletes run in different styles while measuring their oxygen levels at all times. The result was that walking – not running – was most efficient way to stay in shape and <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/fitness/nutrition/15-most-fulfilling-foods-will-help-you-lose-weight" target="_blank">lose weight</a></strong> while being easiest on your body.

The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention <strong><a href="http://www.cdc.gov/physicalactivity/basics/adults/" target="_blank">recommends</a></strong> at least 150 minutes of moderate-intensity aerobic exercise a week. Mathematically, that’s 22 minutes a day or 30 minutes five days a week. This is the minimum amount of time you should brisk walk if your goal is to <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/how-many-calories-should-you-eat-lose-weight" target="_blank">maintain</a></strong> your weight. The new minimum is 250 minutes a week if you want to lose a few <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/8-expert-tips-help-you-lose-last-10-pounds" target="_blank">extra pounds</a></strong>. <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/fitness/technique/best-things-do-look-unbelievably-fit-and-fabulous-over-50" target="_blank">Walk</a></strong> for half an hour a day for maximum effect. As is the case with every workout, your body will adapt. You will eventually need to increase the <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/home-high-intensity-interval-workout" target="_blank">intensity</a></strong> or mileage to achieve the same or better results.

<strong>Walk Well</strong>

Losing about 10 pounds in one month by eating better and walking more is completely<strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/secrets-setting-realistic-fitness-goals-and-sticking-them" target="_blank">realistic</a></strong>, but you have to know how to "promenade" well. When you think of fitness walking, imagine standing tall. <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/fitness/technique/why-proper-posture-crucial-and-how-fix-it" target="_blank">Good posture</a></strong> is where it all starts. Straight back, head forward and swinging arms. Heel-to-toe walking is most efficient. Use your abs and hip flexors to move the legs forward. The best speed is usually just a little slower than when you are about to break into a jog.

<strong>Speed</strong>

Start your walking routine at a moderate speed – about 140 steps a minute. Increase to a brisk pace after a couple of miles. Try speed walking, too. It’s a great aerobic workout that focuses on your legs and also boosts your <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/fitness/your-first-time/which-should-you-do-first-cardio-or-strength-training" target="_blank">cardiovascular strength</a></strong>. Finish a mile in 14 minutes or less. Don’t forget to swing your arms with each step.

Try a little more challenging program when you get comfortable with the speed. Do an interval walk. Complete 3.5 miles in 40 minutes by walking at an easy, quick, as-fast-as-you-can, and brisk speed a few minutes at a time. Walk at a steady pace if your goal is to build<strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/increase-stamina-and-boost-energy-food" target="_blank">stamina</a></strong>. Finish three miles in about 45 minutes. For endurance, you should be able to finish four miles in no more than an hour at a speed of about 135 steps a minute. You’ll have to increase the tempo or the mileage as you become more fit.

<strong>Add weights</strong>

If you want to boost your <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/fitness/n/10-widespread-myths-about-metabolism" target="_blank">metabolism</a></strong>, you must <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/fitness/technique/5-habits-you-must-master-build-more-lean-muscle" target="_blank">build muscle</a></strong>. That can only happen if you do resistance training. So grab a few light weights – 2.5-pound dumbbells, for example – and do bicep curls as you walk. You can also add some exercises for the <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/ace-names-top-three-triceps-exercises" target="_blank">triceps</a></strong>.

As you continue to make your walking workout more challenging, do something different after every lap on the <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/fitness/technique/fitness-tip-day-how-use-treadmill-right-way" target="_blank">treadmill</a></strong> or before every speed change. Good options include burpees, jumping jacks and squats.

<strong>Take the stairs</strong>

This easy trick cannot be stressed enough. Twenty minutes on a <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/fitness/technique/fitness-tip-day-get-stepmill" target="_blank">Stairmaster</a></strong> can equal more than half an hour on a treadmill. You should at least take the stairs going up to your floor at work. A quick walk up and down a few times, followed by 15-25 jumping jacks, is a great cardio drill to boost your health. Bonus: Your glutes are benefitting greatly.

Walking is an exercise; doing more of it will undoubtedly lead to <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/fitness/your-first-time/5-ways-relieve-muscle-soreness" target="_blank">soreness</a></strong>. Don’t forget to stretch. (No <strong><a href="http://www.theactivetimes.com/fitness/technique/try-these-exercises-enhance-your-flexibility" target="_blank">static stretching</a></strong> before working out!) This is the most neglected part of any workout routine but it’s also one of the most important ones. You just walked for an hour. Stretching for 10 minutes is not going to kill you.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>196</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 21:04:16</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 21:04:16</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>how-to-get-in-shape-just-by-walking</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="healthfitness"><![CDATA[Health&amp;Fitness]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[197]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Common Exercises Most People Do Wrong</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/common-exercises-most-people-do-wrong/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=199</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<strong>Fix your form on these exercises, and you’ll be able to do almost anything better</strong>

There were two lat-pulldown stations positioned next to each other in this gym I belonged to many years ago. On one of them was an older woman who was lifting, if memory serves, 10 pounds. I can only assume that she misread the name of the exercise and thought it was a lap pulldown, because that’s where the bar ended up when she rolled it down the front of her torso.

On the adjacent machine was a guy who was lifting, if memory serves, the entire weight stack, or most of it. He rose off the seat at the beginning of each rep to help him get the stack moving, and then leaned back at a 45-degree angle to get the bar to his chest. The deeper he got into his set, the more momentum and body English he employed.

Two people, two completely different ideas about how to do one of the simplest exercises in the gym. And both of them completely wrong.

If you walked into that same gym today, chances are you’d see multiple versions of exercises hardly anyone did a decade ago, like planks and kettlebell swings. Those are in addition to the classic exercises, the simple ones that every lifter has done as long as he’s been lifting, but may not be doing in a way that helps him reach his goals.

“There’s more free information than ever, and yet form hasn’t improved,” says Nick Tumminello, author of the upcoming <em>Building Muscle and Performance: A Program for Size, Strength, and Speed</em>, and a trainer based in Fort Lauderdale. “Men are stubborn, and they always think they know better.”

Flawed exercise form really comes down to three basic problems:
<ul>
	<li>Lack of control</li>
	<li>Poor stability</li>
	<li>Misunderstanding the point of the exercise</li>
</ul>
Let’s tackle them in that order.
<h2><strong>Control issues</strong></h2>
“Most people are in the gym to do bodybuilding,” Tumminello says. That is, to build muscle. But most guys in the gym train like weightlifters, where the goal is to <em>lift the weight</em>. There’s a big difference. “Bodybuilding is about controlling the weight through the entire range of motion.”

Take the lateral raise, for example. The way most guys do it, Tumminello says, is to “swing the weight up, and let it crash down.”

But the entire point of the exercise is to target the middle part of the deltoid muscles. To make them grow, you need to put them under tension. They’re under the most tension at the top of the range of the motion—“the part everyone cheats through,” he says.

You see this over and over in exercises designed to target specific muscles, including the lat pulldowns I described at the beginning. Tumminello also mentions the bent-over barbell row: “They’ll pull it halfway with good form, then jolt it the rest of the way.”

He offers a simple fix:

Select a weight you can hold at the point of maximum tension, with good form. “If you can’t hold it four to five seconds, then the weight’s too damned heavy,” he says. “You don’t<em>need</em> to hold it when you train, but that’s how you should test it.”

For most bodybuilding exercises—lateral raises, lat pulldowns, bent-over or seated rows—you can test your weight at the end of the range of motion. For biceps curls, it’s the midpoint, when your forearms are parallel to the floor.

Or you can make it simpler, and just remember which part of the lift you typically have to cheat to get through. If you can’t hold it there for a few seconds, try using a lighter weight.
<h2><strong>Poor posture</strong></h2>
Picture these four exercises:
<ul>
	<li>Plank</li>
	<li>Pushup</li>
	<li>Loaded carry</li>
	<li>Bear crawl</li>
</ul>
What do they have in common? If you answered, “They’re all the same exercise,” you’re a lot smarter than me. It never occurred to me until Alwyn Cosgrove, my coauthor on the<a href="http://www.thenewrulesoflifting.com/" target="_blank">New Rules of Lifting</a> books, explained it.

Of course they don’t <em>look</em> alike. But the key to good form is exactly the same: Whatever your posture is standing up straight, that’s what it should be when you’re doing a plank, or a moving plank (aka pushup), or a walking plank (aka loaded carry), or a scooting plank (aka bear crawl).

On the plank, pushup, and carry you should be able to draw a straight line from your ears through your shoulders, hips, and heels. On the bear crawl, the line should connect your ears, shoulders, and hips, with your torso parallel to the floor.

The most common mistakes are postural. With the plank, pushup, and bear crawl, you see these almost every day:
<ul>
	<li>sticking your butt in the air</li>
	<li>letting your stomach sag toward the floor</li>
	<li>lifting your head to check out the form of the person in front of you</li>
</ul>
On a pushup, you can tell if you’re lifting your butt when your nose reaches the floor ahead of your chest. If your stomach is sagging on a plank or pushup, you’ll probably feel it as an uncomfortable strain in your lower back. And if you find yourself mesmerized by the person in front of you on any of these exercises, you’re probably lifting your head.

The biggest problems on loaded carries come when the weight is held to one side, as in a suitcase carry. Mistakes might include:
<ul>
	<li>Bending to the side holding the weight</li>
	<li>Overcompensating for the weight by bending to the opposite side</li>
	<li>Leaning back and flaring your rib cage out</li>
</ul>
You can self-correct the first two issues by paying attention. If you’re sober, you should be able to tell if you’re standing up straight. If it’s a struggle, lower the weight.

A good self-check for the latter problem is to place your non-weight-bearing hand on your sternum. If you feel your bottom ribs start to move forward, adjust your posture.
<h2><strong>Cognitive failure</strong></h2>
Return for a moment to the confused woman at the lat-pulldown station, the one pulling the bar down to her hips. Clearly, she didn’t understand that the goal of the exercise is to engage muscles in her middle and upper back, and to do that she needed to select a somewhat challenging weight and pull the bar to her chest.

I remembered it because it’s not something you see every day.

But there are a few commonly misunderstood exercises you’ll see on a regular basis. Tumminello mentions the hanging knee raise. As ab exercises go, it’s about as hard-core as most of us will ever get. But that’s the problem: Most of us can’t actually do the exercise correctly.

To do it right, Tumminello says, you need to tilt your pelvis upward, something that’s hellaciously difficult from a dead hang. Instead, most guys will just lift their knees, a movement that works the hip-flexor muscles on the front of the pelvis but doesn’t work the rectus abdominis, the six-pack muscle, through the intended range of motion.

If you can’t do that pelvic tilt—and as I said, few of us can—then you’re much better served by doing the reverse crunch from the floor or an incline bench.

Another common mistake involves exercises for the opposite side of the torso. When you do a kettlebell swing, the goal is to move the weight by straightening your hips. That engages the powerful glute and hamstring muscles. Your arms and shoulder are just along for the ride.

But before you can straighten your hips, you have to load them by pushing them backwards. If you don’t do that, you can’t generate the force necessary to swing the weight out in front of you. That’s why you see so many people turn the swing into a front raise: they’ll kind of squat down, and then pull the weight up overhead using their shoulder muscles.

A good swing, by contrast, should end up somewhere between waist and chest height. One way to tell if you’re getting it right: the bell goes just a little higher than your hands at the top of the swing, <a href="http://workouts.menshealth.com/exercise/kettlebell-swing" target="_blank">as shown here</a>. If you’re lifting it with your arms and shoulders, it’ll do the opposite, and end up below your hands.
<h2><strong>How to do any exercise better</strong></h2>
The lessons of these nine exercises—lateral raise, bent-over row, plank, pushup, bear crawl, loaded carry, lat pulldown, hanging knee raise, kettlebell swing—can be applied to any exercise you try. You just need to ask yourself three questions:

<strong>1. What is the point of the exercise?</strong>

If the goal is to build muscle, then focus on creating tension in the targeted muscles, and don’t use momentum to blow through that part of the exercise.

<strong>2. What should my body look like while doing the exercise?</strong>

This is trickier, because on many exercises it’s hard to check your form without <em>breaking</em>form to look at yourself. And that’s only if you have a mirror nearby. Without one, you have to pay attention to your body’s signals. If you feel a strain in your lower back on a plank or pushup, that’s your cue to work on your alignment.

<strong>3. What actions should and shouldn’t be involved?</strong>

This is even trickier, and may require coaching, or at least some reading outside the gym. Most people looking at a kettlebell swing would think the goal is to lift the weight up in front of you, so it makes sense that you’d use your arms and shoulders. If nobody tells you it’s all in the hips, how would you know?

Which brings me to perhaps the most reliable cue: When other lifters stop, stare, and then shake their heads as they walk away, you can be pretty sure you’re doing something wrong.

<em>Lou Schuler is an award-winning journalist and contributing editor to </em>Men’s Health<em>. Check out his new book </em><em>Strong: Nine Workout Programs for Women to Burn Fat, Boost Metabolism, and Build Strength for Life</em><em>, with coauthor Alwyn Cosgrove.</em>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>199</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 21:05:19</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 21:05:19</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>common-exercises-most-people-do-wrong</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="healthfitness"><![CDATA[Health&amp;Fitness]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[200]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Why You Should See A Nutritionist</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/why-you-should-see-a-nutritionist/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=202</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Making the decision to see a nutritionist might possibly be the one of the best preventative health care steps you can take. A nutritionist offers much more than just caloric information. They have an abundance of knowledge on how the body functions, which foods are required for maximum performance and how to avoid or prevent certain health pitfalls such as diabetes, high blood pressure, and obesity, to name a few. A good nutritionist can teach you how to eat for the long haul to stay within a healthy weight range an avoid gaining weight back once you’ve lost it.

Here are six things you should know about seeing a nutritionist and how they can help you live your healthiest life.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>202</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 21:13:48</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 21:13:48</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>why-you-should-see-a-nutritionist</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="fooddrink"><![CDATA[Food&amp;Drink]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="healthfitness"><![CDATA[Health&amp;Fitness]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[203]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The New Case for Eating Goat Meat</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/the-new-case-for-eating-goat-meat/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=205</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[You probably eat goat cheese already and know people who drink goat milk—and hey, maybe you do, too. But goat <a href="http://www.eatclean.com/tags/meat" target="_blank">meat</a>? Well, get ready for it, because it may just be the biggest new trend in animal <a href="http://www.eatclean.com/tags/protein" target="_blank">protein</a>.

While goat is a staple in Middle Eastern, North African, and Caribbean cultures, here in the US, the protein-packed lean red meat has flown way under the radar. Now, that's all changing, thanks in part to growing immigrant populations that have helped the import of goat meat shoot up 9-fold over the past 2 decades. During the same time, goat production here in the States has soared by 350%.

So what's all the fuss about? Mainly, goat has a great nutritional profile, with a taste that's just as hearty as beef and lamb. A 3-oz serving of roasted goat has just 122 calories and 23 g of protein—the same size portion of ground beef has the same amount of protein, but for 235 calories. In fact, despite being a red meat, goat has 6 fewer calories per serving than boneless, skinless chicken—not a huge difference, but a big deal, considering chicken's reputation as the leanest meat you can eat.

Goat meat's flavor isn't as gamey as you'd expect, either, with a flavor that's "mild and approachable," says Erin Fairbanks, assistant director of sales at specialty butcher Heritage Foods USA. Other sources describe it as "sweet," "herbaceous," "delicate," and "grassy." (Here are <a href="http://www.eatclean.com/scoops/goat-cheese" target="_blank">6 reasons you should switch to goat cheese</a>.)

True, it's still a bit tricky to find, but it is out there. The best places to find goat are your local specialty butcher, farmers' market, and ethnic markets, says Fairbanks. Make sure you ask for it, too: Even if a retailer doesn't sell goat, he or she may be able to find you someone who does. Online retailers like <a href="https://store.heritagefoodsusa.com/goat-c203.aspx" target="_blank">Heritage Foods USA</a> also sell ground goat, ribs, chops, legs, shoulders, and more.

<span class="storyimage smallfullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" data-attrib="edward westmacott/shutterstock" data-caption="" data-id="52" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:52,&quot;p&quot;:47,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:5}"><img class=" loaded" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpE7VP.img?h=400&amp;w=620&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="" width="620" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;40&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpE7VP.img?h=400&amp;w=620&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" /></span><span class="caption truncate"><span class="attribution">© edward westmacott/shutterstock</span></span></span>

Since goats are similar in size and shape to lambs, most whole cuts can be cooked just like lamb. Goat is also best cooked at low temperatures—since it's low in fat, it can dry out more quickly than richer cuts like marbled steak. For this reason, the meat is best used in dishes that cook low and slow, like curries, stews, and chilis. (<a href="http://heritagefoodsusa.com/blog/category/recipes/goat/" target="_blank">Here are a couple recipes</a> to get you started!)

Not only is goat good for your health, it's also good for the planet. Goat ranchers aren't allowed to use hormones per the USDA, and since most are small-scale farms, animals are usually raised humanely and responsibly. Still, look for "pasture-raised" on labels to make sure you're getting the best, most natural cut of meat from animals fed a natural diet.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>205</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 21:15:11</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 21:15:11</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>the-new-case-for-eating-goat-meat</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="fooddrink"><![CDATA[Food&amp;Drink]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[206]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Follow the New Dietary Guidelines With 15 Dinners Under $15</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/follow-the-new-dietary-guidelines-with-15-dinners-under-15/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=208</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="gallerydata" data-aop="galleryvnext_slidedata">
<div class="show">
<div class="body-text">
<div class="expand"><figure><figcaption>
<div class="caption">
<div>The U.S. Department of Agriculture released <a href="http://www.choosemyplate.gov/dietary-guidelines" target="_blank">new dietary guidelines</a> recently that recommend a "plate" filled with nutrient-dense whole grains, vegetables, and fruits and modest amounts of lean protein. The guidelines take aim at foods linked with obesity, heart disease, and diabetes and urge reductions in the consumption of saturated fats, refined grains, sodium, and added sugar. It may take home cooks a bit of effort to create healthful and satisfying meals in line with the recommendations, but doing so doesn't have to be expensive. Cheapism.com recently cooked up 15 dinners for a family of four that honor the spirit of the dietary guidelines and cost less than $15 each.</div>
</div>
</figcaption></figure></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>208</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 21:19:30</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 21:19:30</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>follow-the-new-dietary-guidelines-with-15-dinners-under-15</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="fooddrink"><![CDATA[Food&amp;Drink]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[209]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>McDonald&#039;s is testing a new breakfast item that&#039;s unlike anything we&#039;ve ever seen (mcd)</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/mcdonalds-is-testing-a-new-breakfast-item-thats-unlike-anything-weve-ever-seen-mcd/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=211</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[McDonald's is reportedly testing a Chicken McGriddle in Ohio.

The sandwich is being tested at 11 locations in Central Ohio, <a href="http://www.bizjournals.com/columbus/news/2016/02/17/mcdonalds-testing-chicken-and-pancake-sandwich-in.html" target="_blank">according to Columbus Business First</a>.

It includes a fried chicken patty wedged between two pancake-like McGriddle patties.

Franchisee Brian Mortellaro said he devised the idea and took it up the supply chain.

"Filet-o-fish, Big Mac – both of those started with owner-operators," Mortellaro told Columbus Business First. "We took this idea up the chain and they’re letting us try it out."

Existing McGriddle sandwiches include a sausage and bacon varieties with cheese and egg.
<p class="content__segment">This isn’t some corporate-mandated rollout. Versions of the product have been tested in other markets before, but this take was devised by <a href="http://www.bizjournals.com/columbus/search/results?q=Brian%20Mortellaro" target="_blank">Brian Mortellaro</a>, who owns eight local McDonald's, and a small group of taste-testers including other operators.</p>
<p class="content__segment">“Filet-o-fish, Big Mac – both of those started with owner-operators,” Mortellaro told me. “We took this idea up the chain and they’re letting us try it out.”</p>
<span class="storyimage fullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" data-attrib="Hollis Johnson" data-caption="McGriddle 2" data-id="50" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:50,&quot;p&quot;:46,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:4}"><img class=" loaded" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpFg9j.img?h=487&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="McGriddle 2" width="728" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;73&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;49&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpFg9j.img?h=487&amp;w=728&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size3column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpFg9j.img?h=417&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size2column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBpFg9j.img?h=417&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" /></span><span class="caption truncate"><span class="attribution">© Hollis Johnson</span> McGriddle 2</span></span>@momo_jackson on Instagram
<p class="content__segment">The Chicken McGriddle has apparently been on the "secret menu" for some time. It's unclear whether the test will be expanded to new markets.</p>
<p class="content__segment">McDonald's is smart to focus on breakfast right now.</p>
<p class="content__segment">The company credited All Day breakfast with a recent <a href="http://www.businessinsider.com/mcdonalds-q4-earnings-2016-1?utm_source=microsoft&amp;utm_medium=referral" target="_blank">surge in sales</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>211</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 21:20:58</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 21:20:58</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>mcdonalds-is-testing-a-new-breakfast-item-thats-unlike-anything-weve-ever-seen-mcd</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="fooddrink"><![CDATA[Food&amp;Drink]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[212]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Subway to roll out its first antibiotic-free sub</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/subway-to-roll-out-its-first-antibiotic-free-sub/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=214</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Subway is taking its first step on the long road toward making all of its meats antibiotic free.

The fast food chain, which vowed to go antibiotic-free last October, will begin selling a rotisserie-style chicken sandwich on March 1 that is made with antibiotic-free, all white-meat chicken that has no artificial color and flavor.

Subway aims to be fully antibiotic-free in the United States by 2025. It plans to convert to chicken products that don't have antibiotics by the end of 2016, all antibiotic-free turkey products in the next two to three years, and all antibiotic-free pork and beef products between 2020 and 2025.

"We have always supported nutrition transparency, 100 percent of the time, and we've done our best to inform our customers of the nutrition values," said Lanette Kovachi, Subway's corporate dietitian. "For about 20 years now, we've put that information out there."

The company says customer demand prompted the ingredient overhaul.

Subway has been trying to burnish its image and move past the public disgrace of its longtime spokesman, Jared Fogle, who recently received a 15-year prison sentence for possessing child pornography and paying for sex with underage girls.

The restaurant brand, which has more than 27,000 restaurants in the United States, cut ties with Fogle soon after the charges came to light.

&nbsp;

The chain is also rolling out a new carved-turkey sandwich to add to its lighter-fare "Fresh Fit" menu, which includes six-inch subs on whole grain bread that are low in saturated fat and come in at less than 400 calories.

Subway has long promoted its healthier-eating option, and lately regulators have been cracking down on restaurants that serve dishes with more salt or sugar than the daily recommended dose.

A judge in New York City recently ruled that some restaurants can be fined up to $600 for not posting salt warnings for some food items on their menus beginning March 1. The decision upheld a regulation from the New York City Board of Health.

"Whatever we need to do to inform the customer, we'll do it," Kovachi said, explaining that Subway already provides salt warnings on a few of its foot-long subs. "If New York City wants us to put a warning label on a menu item, we will do it."

Kovachi says Subway actually reduced sodium in many of its products in 2009 but opted against immediately publicizing the change to customers because some consumers believe low-sodium products to be bland.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>214</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 21:22:06</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 21:22:06</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>subway-to-roll-out-its-first-antibiotic-free-sub</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="fooddrink"><![CDATA[Food&amp;Drink]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[215]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Woman Alleges She Was Hired Then Fired by KFC for Being Transgender</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/woman-alleges-she-was-hired-then-fired-by-kfc-for-being-transgender/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=217</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<em>America still has a lot of catching up to do regarding LGBT rights in the workplace.</em>

As America's <a href="http://www.vox.com/2016/2/29/11132366/john-oliver-donald-trump-last-week-tonight" target="_blank">finest presidential</a><a href="http://www.vox.com/2016/2/29/11132366/john-oliver-donald-trump-last-week-tonight" target="_blank"> candidates</a> criss-cross the country, one side is talking about inclusion while the other preaches a message of <a href="http://www.vox.com/2016/2/10/10956978/donald-trump-terrifying" target="_blank">exclusion</a>, and ideas of acceptance and discrimination are playing out in small, local, everyday ways. Earlier this week a woman in Richmond, Va., claims she was <strong>fired by a local KFC restaurant manager</strong> about an hour after being hired once the manager found out she was transgender.

Georgia Carter contacted a <a href="http://wric.com/2016/02/26/local-kfc-under-fire-for-allegedly-firing-a-transgender-woman/" target="_blank">local TV station</a> in Richmond after she received a phone call from the manager telling her not to come in for training the following day. Carter told a local reporter the restaurant's managers said they could not hire her because her driver's license identified her as a male, and they were not sure which bathroom she could use.

In response to the allegations, and after an internal investigation, KFC's chief people officer John Kurnick released a statement to Eater:
<blockquote><em>"KFC's policy is to treat everyone fairly, equally and with respect, and we do not tolerate discrimination of any kind. Upon learning of this allegation, the franchisee who owns this Richmond restaurant conducted an immediate and thorough investigation. The manager has been terminated for violating the franchisee's anti-discrimination policy, which is inclusive of gender identity and sexual orientation. The franchisee's leadership has also had a conversation with Ms. Carter, offering her employment at this restaurant or any of their Richmond area KFC restaurants, effective immediately. Additionally, the franchisee is emphasizing sensitivity and compliance with their policies to keep this from happening again."</em></blockquote>
This recent incident is just one of a few gender discrimination cases in local restaurants across the United States in the last few months. Back in March one anonymous <a href="http://www.eater.com/2015/3/30/8313959/indiana-restaurateur-discriminate-against-lgbt-gay-lesbian-rights" target="_blank">Indiana restaurateur</a> spoke out about how he already discriminates against LGBT diners. A few weeks ago Chipotle was ordered to pay <a href="http://www.eater.com/2016/2/10/10958414/chipotle-lawsuits-e-coli-gender-discrimination" target="_blank">$600K in a gender discrimination</a> case.

Currently in the state of Virginia, there is no statewide law to protect people from discrimination on the basis of their real or perceived sexual orientation or gender identity and expression in the private or public workplace. <a href="http://www.equalityvirginia.org/what-we-do/ending-discrimination/workplace-discrimination/" target="_blank">Equality Virginia</a> communications manager Brandon Day says Carter has not reached out to the organization, but notes this type of workplace discrimination is all too common around the state. "Like Miss Carter, people just want to work and they are being denied that opportunity just based upon who they, are and that's unfortunate," said Day.

In Virginia a person can legally be fired or refused employment by any employer (large or small) on the basis of that person's real or perceived sexual orientation or gender identity and expression. Day says his organization has been fighting for equal rights for members of the LGBT community since it was founded in 1989. He says during this year's legislative session in Virginia there were four bills that sought to put employment in non-discrimination protection, but those bills did not pass through the subcommittee voting phase. Day notes "there's been a lot of bi-partisan support for passing non-discrimination in employment, but nothing has passed yet."

Day says the organization has recently started the <a href="http://virginiafairness.org/equality-means-business-2/emb-online-directory/" target="_blank">Equality Means Business</a> program in Virginia, North Carolina, and South Carolina, where large and small companies have signed on to say they support the hiring of LGBT employees. The KFC restaurant in Richmond was not listed on the website, but KFC has publicly supported LGBT community issues before. This tweet came from KFC's official twitter account in support of the SCOTUS ruling last summer.

<span class="storyimage smallfullwidth inlineimage" data-aop="image"><span class="image" data-attrib="Provided by Eater" data-caption="image001KFCTweet.jpg" data-id="50" data-m="{&quot;i&quot;:50,&quot;p&quot;:46,&quot;n&quot;:&quot;openModal&quot;,&quot;t&quot;:&quot;articleImages&quot;,&quot;o&quot;:4}"><img class=" loaded" src="http://img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBqaLSm.img?h=449&amp;w=661&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f" alt="image001KFCTweet.jpg" width="661" data-src="{&quot;default&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;66&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;45&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBqaLSm.img?h=449&amp;w=661&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size3column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBqaLSm.img?h=424&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;},&quot;size2column&quot;:{&quot;load&quot;:&quot;default&quot;,&quot;w&quot;:&quot;62&quot;,&quot;h&quot;:&quot;42&quot;,&quot;src&quot;:&quot;//img-s-msn-com.akamaized.net/tenant/amp/entityid/BBqaLSm.img?h=424&amp;w=624&amp;m=6&amp;q=60&amp;o=f&amp;l=f&quot;}}" /></span><span class="caption truncate"><span class="attribution">© Provided by Eater</span> image001KFCTweet.jpg</span></span>

Day says the Equality Virginia organization is hoping to sign up more organizations in the future.

"There is a lot of support coming from businesses, but there are just some places in between that we're still missing," said Day.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>217</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 21:22:58</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 21:22:58</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>woman-alleges-she-was-hired-then-fired-by-kfc-for-being-transgender</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="fooddrink"><![CDATA[Food&amp;Drink]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[218]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Bus-Stop Farmers&#039; Markets Bring Fresh Produce to Food Deserts</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/bus-stop-farmers-markets-bring-fresh-produce-to-food-deserts/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=220</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Chances are, if you're reading this, there's a market selling organic produce just a short walk or car ride away. Don't take this for granted: Millions of Americans live in <a href="http://www.ers.usda.gov/data-products/food-access-research-atlas/about-the-atlas.aspx" target="_blank">"food deserts"</a> where access to fruits, vegetables and other healthy diet options just don't exist. Put another way: Imagine if your only supermarket was the 7-11 and you had no car. What do you feed your family?

Cities across the country have attempted to address this problem, which afflicts 23.5 million, mostly low-income Americans, by establishing farmers' markets in affected areas. Now, organizers are taking a slightly different approach—by setting up shops at local bus stations and other public transit hubs. In the last eight months alone, four cities have launched pop-up-style farmers' markets:

In <strong>Dayton, Ohio,</strong> shoppers can go to a new food source, called <a href="http://www.homefull.org/homefull-solutions/the-market-at-wright-stop-plaza/" target="_blank">"The Market,"</a> which opened in September at Wright Stop Plaza, the main downtown transit center. Homeless people staff the shop, gaining employment experience, local farmers have a new place to sell their bounty, and visitors get vouchers for future purchases to offset costs. It's open four days a week.

A <a href="http://gohart.blogspot.ca/2016/02/farmers-market-coming-to-netprk.html" target="_blank">pilot program</a> launching at the netp@ark Transfer Center in <strong>Tampa, Florida,</strong> is somewhat limited (it's only open on the second Wednesday of each month, from 3pm to 6pm), but patrons can learn how to cook some of the foods they buy—and how to grow them. The USDA contributed $98,000 to make this happen.

Commuters traveling to and from the subway stop in <strong>Atlanta, Georgia'</strong>s West End neighborhood got their own <a href="http://www.acfb.org/sharing-stories/martas-new-fresh-market" target="_blank">market</a> starting last July. It's open only one day a week from spring through fall, but offers fresh produce, cooking demos, a weekly bike tour of nearby urban farms, and information about food assistance programs. If successful, the city will open a farmers market at each of the 37 MARTA stations that make up Atlanta's transit authority.

The largest and most high-profile food hub in the country will open in <strong>Louisville, Kentucky,</strong>later this year. Designed by architect Rem Koolhaus's firm, OMA, the <a href="http://seedcapitalky.org/local-food-economy/louisville-food-port/" target="_blank">West Louisville FoodPort</a> is a 24-acre, $50 million project featuring the largest indoor "vertical" farm in the country, as well as a 60,000-square-foot facility housing retailers, restaurants, and educational organizations. It's expected to generate more than 300 jobs and provide workforce training that can spur development in the local food economy.

Read more about food deserts at the <a href="http://americannutritionassociation.org/newsletter/usda-defines-food-deserts" target="_blank">American Nutrition Association</a>.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>220</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 21:24:04</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 21:24:04</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>bus-stop-farmers-markets-bring-fresh-produce-to-food-deserts</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="fooddrink"><![CDATA[Food&amp;Drink]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[221]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Judge issues temporary hold on NYC salt warning enforcement</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/judge-issues-temporary-hold-on-nyc-salt-warning-enforcement/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=223</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[New York City's enforcement of its first-in-the-nation rule mandating salt warnings on some restaurant menus has been put on hold the day before it was supposed to go into effect.

An appellate judge issued a temporary stay on Monday. The National Restaurant Association had asked for the stay last week, after another judge ruled the city could fine restaurants that don't comply with the labeling rule up to $600, starting on March 1.

The rule, enacted in December, calls for chain restaurants and fast-food places with more than 15 outlets nationwide to put triangle icons with salt-shaker images on menus next to items that go above the recommended daily limit of sodium. That's 2,300 milligrams, about a teaspoon. High salt intake can raise health risks including high blood pressure and heart disease.

A judge had ruled last week against the restaurant association's challenge of the rule. The association is appealing, and filed for the stay of enforcement while the appeal is underway.

The group "is pleased by today's decision to grant emergency relief for the men and women that own and operate New York's restaurants from this unlawful and unprecedented sodium mandate. We look forward to a full and fair opportunity to make our case before the Appellate Court."

The city's Department of Health said the warnings are critical information people need, and that it was confident the rule would be upheld.

The department "will continue to warn chains if they are not compliant, but will not issue violations while the stay is in place."

The city has until March 18 to respond to the injunction.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>223</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 21:24:49</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 21:24:49</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>judge-issues-temporary-hold-on-nyc-salt-warning-enforcement</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="fooddrink"><![CDATA[Food&amp;Drink]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[224]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>This Market Exclusively Sells Food Other Stores Would Have Thrown Out</title>
		<link>http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/2016/03/01/this-market-exclusively-sells-food-other-stores-would-have-thrown-out/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://truewordpress.com/wordpress/?p=226</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[My grandfather used to tell me that expiration dates are just a suggestion; it doesn’t necessarily mean the food can’t be eaten. He was right. Not that I’d trust eating half the things in his fridge, but he was right. As we <a href="http://www.foodandwine.com/fwx/food/should-you-be-eating-18-month-old-expired-food-usda-suggests" target="_blank">discussed last year</a>, even the USDA admits, “There is no uniform or universally accepted system used for food dating in the United States.”

A supermarket in Denmark has taken that idea to heart. WeFood only sells food that would have been discarded by other grocery stores. Expired food, damaged food or any surplus in general: As long as it’s edible, WeFood wants what other business would have thrown out.

The values behind the market, which was started by a non-profit, aren’t about finding a way to make a buck where other companies couldn’t. Instead, WeFood hopes to cut into some of Denmark’s 700,000 tons of annual food waste while offering inexpensive shopping options to people who are concerned about their budget, the environment, or both.

“WeFood is the first supermarket of its kind in Denmark and perhaps the world as it is not just aimed at low-income shoppers but anyone who is concerned about the amount of food waste produced in this country,” <a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/denmark-food-waste-supermarket-we-food-copenhagen-surplus-produce-a6890621.html" target="_blank">said Per Bjerre</a> who works for Folkekirkens Nodhjelp, the organization behind the store.

The market hopes to sell produce for up to 50 percent less than other grocery stores. They already have an agreement with one of the country’s biggest grocery chains for bread, as well as agreements with fruit importers, butchers and other food producers. And much like the unique <a href="http://www.foodandwine.com/fwx/dutch-supermarket-sells-food-those-who-can-afford-it-gives-it-away-those-who-can-t" target="_blank">Dutch grocery store Swingmarket</a> that we looked at earlier in the week, WeFood also relies on the help of volunteers.

My grandfather would love this concept. Have they considered opening a location in Florida?]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>226</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-03-01 21:25:38</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-03-01 21:25:38</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>this-market-exclusively-sells-food-other-stores-would-have-thrown-out</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="fooddrink"><![CDATA[Food&amp;Drink]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="lifestyle"><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[227]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_widget_position</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[l]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_adwords_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_ads_embed</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>page_breadcrumb_active</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[on]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_facebook</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[facebook.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_twitter</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[twitter.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_google</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[plus.google.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>post_linkedin</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[linkedin.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
